Hi guys
Good babe. Hi, you're sleeping
Those right there
Sleepin deal
Hi guys, how's everyone tonight?
Have a nice Saturday night
I'm sorry I have a pretty easy night tonight. I might get some food later, but
Now I'll just hang out smoke a babe. What's up guys?
Hi
Rudy's right here, too
There's three cats in the couch, so full couch
Can everyone hear me okay?
Come on in
Thank you for being here tonight Saturday night is the 20th 620
And now it is close to the winters or those are the summer solstice
There's anything important today, June 20th.
Hi, everybody.
It was Juneteenth yesterday, let's see.
So today is American Eagle Day.
National take your dog to work day.
The ugliest dog day.
national saluma light therapy day. Can you believe that?
National hike with the geek day. Do you want to do that with me? National ice cream soda day. Holds that to the SGM 20th. Hi, bisquick!
Um, yeah, I just did start two minutes ago, so it's not gonna take a few minutes.
I've been doing this for long enough not to be worried about numbers. I'm already monetized.
There
Someone's so nice now
There's people there's people. I know I have a lot of we've a lot of common audience and they can be one or the other
I'm doing fine. I'm not complaining
If it does low down, oh for all same as someone always Sam and if I use the same on his salmon was one of the people that helped me
Be I mean be to help me say I'm gonna help me so whenever or at least to help me whenever they're on
please
Just for you to
Hold on you lost
My
Lester
Think so
Shining bright like a diamond
Now my luster spine lustrous and my luminous aura times 10,000. I was the instrument for like a week or two. Well
Went to my head I never thought I was geez
Requiem for a dream hi Dusty
Yeah, this is my luster if you go to my head and I didn't go to my head. I didn't like
You know do something ridiculous with it
Now you have a great video for me. I've seen requiem for dream. What's your video? I have to watch it off. I'll scan with it
I'll check it out
Yeah, we're just gonna start here
You know seriously like five in the morning six in the morning. I had like 40 50 people in the chat, so I'm doing fine
Hey, Dusty, yeah, it's kind of like
How do you send it you can just
Put the link in the back chat or I'm on Instagram or discord
Like he awakens on both his places look me up
Yeah, but you know, I'm also um, you know
It's true a lot and on the issue. Thank you. I think he does that you're awesome, too
Thank you so much. Yeah, but it's you a lot on YouTube been through lots of
ups and downs been through some
you know friendships that kind of
So we're so really so we're going really well some summer and suffer a little bit
But I'm doing my best learning
Haven't fun so long have fun. I'll do this, you know even if I
To cut down like many hours. I would still do it probably almost every day, but maybe just as many hours
But it's fun. I was like I was just sitting around today watching TV watching some tarot on TV and
Hey, how's the cat? I was like, I was like, I just like hanging out with like here. It's fun. It's like, it's more socialized and so
Thank you, Dusty. Yeah, so
Also, I don't know, this quick you're like kind of saying I'm like, I was the flavor of the month, soon or the week or something or
Think I was got success. I don't but it's like
Consider this I am probably in like the 1% of
People making money on YouTube and that's I mean, there's even if it's a very small amount
There's a big amount of people, you know, hi mojo Joe
So, you know, I feel like
You know only 5% of people on YouTube even have a
Channel let me or have content on a channel
Subscribers like 5% of everybody with a YouTube account. So there's like 2 billion people with YouTube accounts
So there's probably like, you know over 100 million channels, but
Still a very small percentage
But I wouldn't do I thought want to really encourage like a lot of
My you know people that are my chats and peers and things like that to check out open panels check out
Starting your own channel streaming
I think that it's really untapped like it's thinking it can be much more like many more people
You know, there's like people can worry about. Oh, you know, well, he has this audience
He's this audience there's people with over a million viewer. I mean, so it's like
basically
$100,000 it's nearly 3 a.m. Oh wow, it's hot there
It's pretty warm today, so it's 6.45 p.m.
The sun's still out. I'm Rudy. I'm here with Rudy.
You know, I have a copyright song, so you won't play it or send it on me.
Thank you, Dusty. Thank you. Yeah, I just have to be careful, you know, with all people's content.
But I appreciate you just sending the link also if you want so you can try to go backstage
Don't to come on the show you can if they have a private chat the backstage where you will be able to post
Any link you want if you feel like it. I'll check it out
How's your guys your day you want to that's me yeah
Yeah, it's it's like I know you I know you all and I know like most people wouldn't
you know
It's surprising if I didn't know better though like with some people like because some people will continue to oh
Please do please don't they're still want me and it's like
You might hate me or laugh oh, it's okay. Oh, no, it's like making fun of me
Well, I thought I wouldn't like
Not like the cartoons that were made of me like I was like I was send them before I just didn't watch them
I say oh, that's gonna make fun of me or something. I don't look like dumb
Well, I just gotta tell you something yeah, yeah change the name of your title, you know, it's Friday, right? Oh
It's Friday ocean. Yeah
Yeah, that's it makes you look crazy when you don't know what day it is understand
Well, maybe I'm a little bit crazy. Who knows there picks up. Thank you. Let me know
I was trying to be nice to you. All right, you're fine. You're fine. It's okay, you know
Sometimes my days blend together a little bit. It doesn't feel like a Saturday here, but it is a Friday
He has to write your correction. No, you didn't change it. Okay. I was letting you know
Thank you
I'm trying to do sorry, but yeah, you you've lost track of time. Yeah, this is me to you
That was you too. Yeah, no, I have a very
Strange sleep schedule. And so, you know, it happens sometimes
Tomorrow will be Saturday
Okay. Well, I'll probably stream so long today that you know, there would have been right eventually, but yeah
I'm glad I glad I fixed the yes. I do. I know I'm sick
Well, why are you done? I was just trying to be nice. You're nice. You're nice Friday. It was this Saturday, right?
I don't know. I thought it was that
Yeah, because
I don't know because the other day I thought it was like gonna be Friday was and I woke up on Thursday. I was like, oh shit
Yeah, that happens
But I was just I don't know if you saw Mike that's on this
Streamer named Lord of the Groove. I don't know if you know who they are
I don't I don't really watch out there. Oh, you don't anymore. Okay. Oh
Just telling a chat. Yeah, I'm only subscribed to like four or five streamers
But you can yeah finisher story. Oh, yeah. Well, I was just telling someone made these three cartoons of me like using my
You know my some clips for my show and I was easy. What's up?
I was like, oh, no, they're gonna make fun of me
But then I actually people so go watch them and I actually watched them
There's like a minute of each but never actually very funny. So I
Yeah
Yeah, and
I got great very funny people in my chat. What's up easy Harry mojo Joe, you know, I like but last night was just pretty crazy like
It was just like one after another people just kept
Doing something that caused me to end the stream and if this kept doing it
And then I would say right when it started to them or to when they were in the chat of say hey
Don't say this and then they would say it again. And so it kind of is like
I'm like wondering what some people will not listen to you and I'll just keep doing it. I
Know but I'm just wondering if it's like they don't know it
He go he go don't tell me and don't tell me I'm not moaning. I'm just uh, you know, it's interesting that
You know, it's either they are just unable to
Understand which is like kind of scary like you know
I can I can alter my behavior, you know, we can all go to a different environment and
Alter our behavior. You're repeating. Oh by the way. Oh, thank you. Oh, thank you
Yeah
Yeah, so
And then but also the more also the more you I bring attention to that
I so I think I try not to like harp on the rules because then people will just want to break them and so
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it
I mean, but it's like I know I I know I I've understood that and it's like, you know, but like really
People that try to take channels that I don't understand because
Like how's my shit? I don't understand how I've been shrewd on anyone's life
I've never like, you know, I'd understand if I went around attacking streamers
You walked it on the wrong fucking community. I
Walked the wrong community
I'm saying you walked in on the wrong community and you're not getting on your stand at, you know, not gonna understand it
Well, maybe I'm not going to be like I've been trying to help you her. Hey. Oh, yeah
So say he's mad at me. Oh, please be mad at me. Probably but I think we're fine. We're fine
It is a well-made mojo Joe. It is but also
Like it's like I said, it's already a modern Benny Blancos and then Triton's and then I was a modern Saints
I was a mod for Emma and so these they had they've had they had a crazy trolls and so I saw a step in the chest and I
Yeah, we'll be with those friends
I can tell you something some trolls are smarter than others
Mm-hmm. Just wait till the cops are trying to pound your door in they already have that happened a couple months ago already, so
Well, it's not down my door. No, I'm I'm telling I'm trying to tell you something. You don't understand
No, well, because you don't understand. Oh, oh wow. Well, you know
He's getting a little aggro. I was just trying to tell him that yes
I've already been dox. I've already had the police at my house
They've already had a hundred pizzas sent over. I mean, I don't understand what trolls are
I've kind of have dealt with them every day for like the last
You know six months. What's up, Maya?
Yeah, it's like, you know
See that was an example of he comes on. I'm trying to help you. Okay. I'm trying to help me
No, he doesn't like me very much. He only comes on usually when Crystal Marie is here or
He's told me like I wasn't not bought. I was in love his pants. He said he didn't like my energy was and I
Have no problem with him. Okay, but he's sitting there like he's he's not he's not he's not he's not a monetized streamer
Okay, he's not
I mean, right
So I mean if he has you know karaoke and listen to music and does what he wants. I mean, that's fine, you know, but
So he's explaining to me about trolls and channels and stuff, right?
You understand it's like it's like that's kind of like the man's playing even though I am a man
But I understand how women can get so you're you know how
Like mansplaining, I'm sure everyone knows what it is,
and he was me explaining it, I'm mansplaining it now.
Now mansplaining, all it means is like
giving a kind of snarky or condescending
or a snobby explanation about something
like the person's never gonna heard of it, right?
You're worth the trolley reform?
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I even,
Like there's many different kinds of shoulders. He said some shoulders are smarter than others. Well
Yeah, okay. Yeah, well some people are smarter than others and there's all kinds of people in all kinds of professions and all that stuff, right?
So you were yeah, and so this is running wild. Is it 2020?
Are you in a good mood 2020 or are you yelling at me and shadowing me again?
So anyway
Um, well, thank you for the help good times. No
With that nirvana song forever in debt to your priceless advice
So
Yes, I did accidentally put the wrong title at first and thank you for being that's my attention, but I
don't know that I did
Okay, thank you for being on the show
Never lose the coat Pico. Oh
Three times go wash. Okay. Yeah, it's like, I don't know. I just want to tell you
I'm trying to help you
Scrolls, you don't know what a troll is
You're gonna get in route and now
And you're gonna give me a 100% straight. Okay good
Good time is mad
There's okra's
That was my fault
The
Alex first came right out of the jerk still is but he's entertaining. Yeah, I agree. Yeah, he's also
He's
Kind he's kind half the time half the time he's a little bit
a little bit much, lately he's been just on his conspiracy theories about the panel
verse and he thinks everyone is everyone else, like under a different identity, and I'm
sure there is some of that going on. Yes, Gwed Smith tells. I'm sure there is some of
that going on, but I don't think it's that big of a conspiracy. I think it's, hmm,
Yes, there's a band in my chat at home, but I'm bad everyone you get your way kids tarot
Go for it. So yeah, it's from the beginning of America from the founding of America until the first eight until
The first day of 26 is 91 26 days
That's cool
Well, this no this is unbanned, but they were I think they were a mod at one time
Then they did they put gets away kids tarot. That was the count was banned for a short time. I've unbanned everybody so
No, not 926 I don't but what is it like that so oh, it's 91 days
It's 91. I but was what's the uh, is that numerology you're trying to tell me or is there some kind of like little?
Code or message in that or it's just an interesting fun fact
It's your better half. Okay. Well, I'm you know, I have no problem because I don't know
Okay. Yeah. Oh
I see. Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. My eyes are a little bit blurry
My lacy might be starting to wear off
And it played 25 years ago. It's 91 or 9-1-1
Yeah
That is a interesting number
Yeah, always gonna be associated with that horrible thing
Okay, oh yeah, man. Hold on. I trust you Smith. Hold on
Hello, man, I don't want to be on camera, but I just showed you've seen me before. Okay. It's been a long time
Okay, how big are you though, bro?
How big am I?
Yeah, I just I think I'm sick of you a few hits of the vape
I just almost a few bits a few hits of the vape and I have a
Some of my twists and tear or I think it's actually Arizona hard Arizona iced tea to drink in a couple other drinks and
I don't do much panels anymore, but you totally slaughtered what I was trying to do what I was trying to the message
I was trying to convey to people that from the founding of America until the first day of 26 is
911 to six days like an emergency like 9-1-1
26 what do you think you the first day of 2 6? What does that mean like the first day of 2026? Oh
Yeah, that makes sense. Okay, so 26 is Z
Z is the last letter of the alphabet. America is the alpha country. It's the end of alpha. Bet. Bet.
So that would be, um, so alpha is would be one, one, two, five.
The alpha country, and if you look at the three eclipses, they made the alpha sign over America.
The last eclipse was under the sign of Cetus the whale, but for the wicked generation,
there will be no sign except for the sign of Jonah, which is why the eclipse was under Cetus the whale.
It's not numerology though. People always want to pin me in the numerology
I'm not gonna tell you that now other than I said 9-1 is an emergency everyone knows that like 9-11
It is numerology in a way in that you you're you're catching meaning even though it's not some kind of no
No, that's the only that's the only time you let me attach a meaning other than that
I just count the days because God's numbered them for us
Hmm. You know what I mean? Yeah
Well, if you do look into like numbers and patterns, I mean it's like I do people a lot of people do just like pick
In shoes from different systems. They can make the words whatever about you know, yeah
Yeah, I don't do that. I think that's your mattress stuff is so fake and a distraction and
This is this that's not interesting to me. I don't do that. Mm-hmm. No
I found it mildly interesting, it is like what I have seen people fall into rabbit holes
of it or even to the point of insanity almost, from getting obsessed with the numbers and
the meanings and thinking that everything is just so connected, I mean things are connected
but
There's so many variables that it's like you can connect a lot a lot of things no matter what do anything
Oh, check out check out this variable. So in math the variable is x very is a synonym for so
You got that mm-hmm. So very a bowl or so Toro, you know what I mean, uh-huh very so Toro
He's very old so Toro Toro me
That's like that's Obama's name or something. Yeah, yeah, Toro means bull. His name is so Toro
He's very old and the variables X now listen to this X is she X is she and she is Chicago
And where's he from Chicago the bulls the buy bulls from Chicago him and his husband
Yeah
So I'll get back people I'm gonna start putting out content again because I think people need to hear it
Yeah, I think people just think it's it's just gonna be fun and games for it's not it's not so take care
Okay, well
Interesting, I mean I was just again. I don't know who this person is Clears. Who are you?
Can you get a terrible thing? Sure. Are you a nice person?
Can you just like wave to me on camera or something to prove that you're I just I had a lot of people come in and try to start trouble
So hold on yes, you get a terrible, you know
Or let me see
Okay, it's really old. Oh, yeah guys. I hope I don't get this. Hold on
Yeah
No, I won't be letting you on you can ask that. Yeah, you can ask a question from the chat. Oh
But yeah, that person just wanted to say the n word a bunch of times. Yeah, hey
Who are you talking to Smith? Are you talking to me or somebody else in YOLO?
Okay, I owe you a Pico. It's what 11 9 and 9% of the world. Yeah, nine and 90% of the stretch
Yeah, I mean, that's what it's like. There's so like, you know numerical systems and alphabetical systems. They're all
From the human mind, they're all human systems. Yeah, I
Know because of because of the nice guy because of mom
But it's interesting Smith because I just wanted to say like you're like, okay
Well, it's gonna get really bad and it's like I don't know if it's bad because it's based on just
That coincidence of the the 2060. I mean, I still have to look back. I know the number 911 comes up, right?
Yeah, yeah, I will
So, yeah, but it's funny that people said I look like Agent Smith, but it is interesting
to think about, but I do think that kind of thought, if you say the 901s, so that's the
only thing that number we find, if you do attach me to.
And I don't know, I'd be more interested to hear what you think is going to happen, but
Yeah, there's been a lot of bad stuff predicted throughout the years and most of it that never comes to pass
it just scares a lot of people and
You wanna see Lola, here's Lola. Lola, do you wanna say hi everybody? Miss Lola
You're back there Trix too
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know. It's it's like it is a little slow. I know I know there's people on right now
I don't know. What should I get for dinner? I'm hungry
Why do they have it on a
Everyday they have some kind of value menu at Subway
But I forgot what they have on Friday, so let me check what they have a Friday. Where's my phone? Do you ever see my phone?
Hey mojo joe hey, uh, okay two trumps. Okay, okay
Okay
But Smith that's the kind of thing I'm talking about with like the rat like the people find the rabbit holes over it because you can
Look you can just play with people can play with the numbers and then attach meaning to them
I was too crowded once that okay, they look for the coincidences, but
be careful about attaching meaning to anything.
It's like, look at things very scientifically.
I kind of do a lot.
Oh, is there a jobs crazy?
Is it Lola's?
You have to attach meaning.
The Bible already did. Yeah, y'all are you bored though? Am I boring? Well, yeah, he's sleeping right next to me.
What happened 90s? I don't know. It's like there's people on it's kind of early and kind of maybe people are other places.
I have like 50 people this morning. Also, unfortunately, I have had to like restart my stream several times
because people keep fucking with me trying to get me to restart. And then I don't know who you are in the backstage.
Let me know who you are. Do I know you? Why are you here?
Yeah, I know you guys the things will go up to the ups and downs
I you know I have more people here than I did
When I first started streaming, you know, I probably had three to three to five, but I first started so
Yeah, yeah, but I understand the Bible doesn't have very interesting stuff in it
Interesting codes that you can you even have a whole thing called it's called numbers
They have a whole numbers part of the Bible. So so who is black?
Black ween home here
Okay, so no, I'd not like you on
Okay, and
the oh
I mean, I was I wasn't talking to you. I've met the other person, but you left you. I'll let you on. Well, okay
My better Joe, thank you for me. I welcome
shout out to psyche dude psyche is a real one bro psyche psyche I've been I
have been a guest on psyche stream since he had nobody in here bro shout out to
him yep well
that
Oh, yeah, he's saying he's saying he wants to join and he was pre you let him on
Yeah
Alright, I'll put him the link for him dude. I literally bro. I um, we were talking, right?
How do I prove that I'm straight?
Because he was saying that I'm gay and I'm trying was asking him to prove that I'm straight
I'm reformed chat stop stop being weird chat. I'm reformed. I'm reformed now. I'm not an insult. I respect women
All right, I'm reformed. Yeah, that's good
This is like you've grown up a lot you've matured. No, I'm reformed now, so okay, okay?
We'll see we'll see what happens. I'm not gay chat. No, I okay
of it, but no we really can't you are not me
300 gold keeps trying to say
that I'm fucking gay
and I'm trying to, and I asked him
how do I, then how do I
prove to you that I'm, that I'm straight
then
well make out with him in front of
make out with Flurry Diamond in front of him
that's not going to prove that I'm straight
that's going to prove that I'm gay
because Flurry Diamond is a
a born
Yeah, she is all all due respect
All due respect long time. I know are you well? I don't follow this nigga this nigga 300 go every time he joins the stream
I need to follow your channel, bro
Yeah, it's right. What's what's your YouTube channel? What's the cope every time this nigga joins the stream 300 go?
Go has to pose
that's crazy and he's calling me gay
that's crazy
we're waiting
That's crazy. What's up with the neck hair? There's nothing wrong with my neck hair
I just wanted to I just wanted to be like if if my head if I flip my head upside down
It still looks like I have hair on top of my head. You know what I mean? Thank you psychic
Okay, it's in the back chat
that's it. Let's see. So, it's
going to draw a tag with a
bunch of big black decks
around for you. Yo, yo, so
psyche. So, we came on here,
right? Me and Signal, we're
having this conversation where
where he needs to prove
where he needs to prove that
he's straight. Okay. And then
we're telling him to show
and then he ran over here to you, so I don't know how that's gonna help his, um, the proof, but, okay, so we're here
well, I still, I don't think this thing is gay, but, does this thing, you're not, you're not by curious at all?
nope
never, okay
you never try this thing, you don't, you know you wouldn't like it
no, that's crazy
Say what if you like I'm just saying it's hypothetical. I hope it never happens
But what if some day you you know, what if you got like a life in prison and then you you're never to get out or see
That's crazy. Yeah, but what would you do? Would you like just like
Settle in or would you like really bad, bro?
Well, I don't know. I would have to be in the situation that even think about that, but I'm not gonna be gay, you know
Yeah, and Mojo Joe says nobody cares about your sexuality. Let's see. We will see that's why that's why it's good
That's it came here because it's gonna be a less judgmental
Judgmental, you know chat about that's actually, but so I get some shit, but I don't think you're gay
I mean, it's like it's really bad if you give a shit, huh? It's yeah
Where nobody cares if he's gay right now
Yeah, I'm not though. He's not I'm not gay though
I'm not gay though
It's like when I like, you know, it's like like most guys would just say I'm not gay all the time
You know and stuff like that if they were secure about it, but most guys not gay though
I know you're not but they have to keep repeating that and like letting us know just because just
I'm this guy is just saying that I'm gay because he wants me to be gay
Okay, that's 300 glows back. You're married. Are you think we're going to go?
300 blow wants me to be gay
That's true. It's very low. That's true. I have a wife
Yeah, he's exactly what makes it even crazier
He's married with a wife
And he's still a gay man, but I respect that
I'm straight why are you guys want me to be gay so bad
It's like I would I wouldn't want you to be gay because I already heard your sir about your dirty butthole from 40 diamond
It turned me off completely. What?
Remember when you hear about what you like tear shit on her stream and he moves her with like a
No
What you did that's what has never happened
Well, then she's fucking lying. She's told the story at least 10 times on my show. I mean, well, that's not true
Okay
the
I do have I do have the ability to psyche. You know how many people psyche
You know how many people I've put on to rumble and now they're on the creator program making money
You know how many cool? I mean I can do it
Three like three four people like three four people and you can restream to YouTube as well
You don't have it doesn't have to be one or the other
Well, I'm telling you right now, bro. I'm trying to put you on bro
Like I said, I have the ability on stream yard to stream to multiple platforms including I think rumble
and so, you know, I can do it all from stream yard, you know
And just have them go everywhere, but I
Like I'm going I know YouTube sometimes this low and it's like, you know
You can be slow going, but I knew that going and I knew we just be very slow and it happened
It's happened on YouTube for me faster than
Um, you can add that to 27th suit. Thank you. Let's just for a few minutes flirty
30 times 300 has a
You guys are haters, bro
So your chat is full of haters. It's like just ignore this just ignore the chat
They get it, you know, really just your chat is full of haters and then the worst part is that you guys are haters
And then you make up and then your haters again, and then you make up
And then you well here's again. That's just like corny. Honestly. Did you niggas ever think about showering going outside and getting a job?
Well, here's the thing. I've done that many times. I can say 300 gold does that
Actively I have I have considered
Getting a job and going outside and showering
But I don't I don't know. I think I'm good, bro. I think I'm good
Think I'm chilling bro. I think I'm chilling bro. I make my money when I need to make it, bro. I
Get my dough knows I'm rumble, bro. I'm getting money
I'm chilling bro
And when we need to make money we make money, bro
What held you back what do you mean sick is an angry incel I'm not an angry incel
maybe I was an angry insult, but I'm not an angry insult anymore. No, I'm just
Think it's just angry
No, I'm just angry
You just go over like you get like a you know a nice outfit go to a gay club
You know what I'm gonna do. You know what I'm gonna do
But bro people think bro
hmm
Bro, I'm gonna I'm gonna do I'm gonna go I'm gonna go
I'm gonna get me a Honda Civic beater
All right, and I'm gonna do a road trip stream
All right
And whoever wants to link up along the way we link up with them
What do you mean? We're gonna make it and we're gonna make it to California
where I'm gonna where I'm gonna meet up with 300 glow and I'm gonna have sex with him on stream
It's not gonna be and it's not gonna be gay though
It's not in the gateway
You know, it's gonna be it's gonna be consensual and straight
All right
Cheers shot cheers
Thank you for you remember. Thank you remember. I'm in California too, right? So
Well, I'd be invited to the party. I don't think I'm I don't know psyche. I think you tell me sometimes
You know I have a threesome. I think psyche is gonna. I think psyche with roof. Yes, bro
No, I would I would have to do it. I wouldn't do anything. You just do this way back and close your eyes. You were roof
Yes, that's no, I would I would not be drunk
Let's say if I was a single woman he said sex with say are you a virgin thing or no?
Yeah, I'm a birch
I've never had sex in my life. Nobody has ever touched me sexually before
Oh, I guess that's true
That's true
Brows boring boning bros. Yeah, but I really think I've seen I think nowadays there is like so much like
You know if they're not gay it's like the guys are just like well like
Play it like to play around a lot of people do that on YouTube. It's people just they play around with each other and like
Access and they get the people's reactions and stuff
The world's getting kind of gay
We can play with each other
We could play with each other's penises literally literally yeah
Well the thing is and then it's like that I try to I try to like join on the fun and joking and that everyone gets offended and says
I'm I'm harassing them. Oh, it's that it's cool. It says birthday. Oh, thank you. Wake and I'll put it on the full screen
Oh, thank you. I love the I love the lettering
The quote that be close. I see you
Yeah, I said my I bet yeah, it's my say there's a there's one I can't remember her name
Like 60, okay, okay masturbation. Okay. Oh, yeah
Terrier does yeah
Yeah, so the chat is gonna have a question
Yeah, it's a man question. Look at you. That's his broke back mountain outfit. Are you know, are you gonna get cowboy hat shoes?
Yeah
It's broke back stick and
He you know, he likes to cuddle in the sleeping bag. There's some way of showing affection. I can't wait. I don't even mean but yeah, okay
Yeah, so we're doing some blinkers, bro. We're doing some fucking blinkers. Oh, yeah, well, I did a couple
There's anyone thing a guy we're the chat thing is it's a gay or like you have any advice for sick to discover sexuality
Let's say no
I'm straight and I like women and I want a woman to love and care about me
And I don't want a man to love and care about me. That's my answer
you know you okay you don't mean to love you okay
well I mean that's my answer okay 300 glow left why did he go
because he was you insulted him by I insulted him
you made a big you made a big joke out of you know he wanted to keep up with you
he said a million times the age
have you ever heard the saying thou doth protesteth
I've never heard that sound. I think it's from Romeo.
No, I've never heard it. No.
It means that, it means that, yeah.
But all it means is like,
when you like,
he'd say, he'd deny something.
Even if it's not true,
he'd deny it.
It kind of sounds like...
Does SIG buy his clothes in the kids' section?
What does that even mean?
We have to be like, yeah.
I don't even I don't even I'm half the time. I'm not wearing it. Sure. What does that even mean?
I think I think city shops like that extra extra extra large
Like it was sun dresses on on a home shopping network and
Where's one of those occasionally, but otherwise I just didn't make it
See you never leaves that basement. Yeah, exactly. I guess I walked into that one a little bit
This is a 30 year old man that acts like he's 12 years old. That's what it means. I
guess
Hey, that's like a
I am precise way to say it. Yeah, I know this guy is
I'm not a fan of his this guy doesn't like me either
Yeah, I never said that this guy's well you've done you've done this such
So you can enjoy your stream with this guy. I'm not going to leave you leave me. What's going on?
Why are you mad at this guy?
He's like him your sky this guy has this guy. You know what? He did one time psyche
One time he edited he chopped together and edited a super weird clip of
Me saying some crazy shit and then played it for hours on the stream
No, he did that once
Yeah, I don't like this guy. I'll see you later psyche. Okay letting me out. Hey my say wow
I've never seen say leave reggae. Oh, what did you do mr. Big Pipes?
I'm telling you this is like the fifth time that's happened with people like they all like spurred out
I'm like the chillest person dude. I swear
Did you ever make a clip of him or anything or no? No, I was just making it up. Okay. What is the stop process?
Yeah, well, I was gonna stream a little bit but I wanted to drink some vodka first
Okay, yes, cool. I have a harder lemonade. We can
Have some have some
Alcohol, they said it had bad sex. That's why oh
Have you been saying it, you know, he's just trying to chill. Oh, yeah, he's just trying to chill. It's so weird man
I'm like the chills dude over I was gonna go this rave tonight. I got invited to rave, but I
Don't know I talked myself out of it
Yeah, I've
Made you a raven probably over 20 years, but I would like to go to one
But I know I think I'm first of all, there's not that many of them anymore. It's second of all. I probably I think I'm
too old though
Oh, come on guys. Everyone be nice to the guests. They want to come up to say hi to Mr. Bigpipes. What are you doing tonight, Mr. Bigpipes? You're just going to chill with the bottle and do some streaming?
Yeah, I'm going to stream in like an hour probably. I'm going to get like four or five shots of vodka on me first.
Well, that's a lot.
So, yeah, I'm not good if I'm not 50 years old. Sorry. I'm 44
So, yeah, I think I'm probably maybe too old but I didn't see these scribbles
You know if you're a scribble's IRL he was just had a rape with his brother and they're like it's like a 40 or 50s
Thank you. I really eat your
Well, I was gonna go to a bluegrass. Oh, yeah, so it's like I had a choice like I couldn't go to a bluegrass pick
Or I could go to the rave
I got invited by like both people, but actually there's like a combination. There's like
Bluegrass Ravers to like mm-hmm. Well, yeah, that'd be interesting. Well, that'd be interesting having her
It exists like these like electronic
You have like like black light banjos and like, you know, my kind of like
They have a blue grass room since then said he's gonna drink alone and streamed. Oh come on blacker. We'd be nice
I don't know. I keep reading. Okay
Well, you know, I don't I don't really go out at all like
Still go actually, it's probably gonna be going on all night. I just don't want to like I'd have to go down town
I got like get back like I just don't want to have to get back. I
Could probably got in a ride there too. I don't know but then I got it like
It'd be like a 40 or 50 dollar Uber
Yeah, I mean those ubers get expensive right now and
No, I prefer like to stay home like and uh, you know have a nice, you know
My scene like I don't really like the electronic stuff that much like I'm not a big like
I'm trying to think the last time I like danced at a concert. It has to be like
12 or something shit, maybe 2014
like
the Motet and Boulder I believe
Or like a Herbie Hancock cover band my song
Well, I haven't been out a long time but
If I do go anywhere this year, I do hope to go to Florida for a few days and
Now be good enough for ten years, I'll be happy for ten other ten years
But it's been probably over ten years since they did anything when anywhere for any overnight, right?
Yeah, so are you feeling like a little better mood tonight?
I know you've been kind of, you know, a little bit cranky and we're, we're just appearances
and everything.
Okay.
Are you talking to me?
Yeah.
I am I'm showing I'm always okay. I'm chill until like you get to get some dork on your like threatening me and shit
Well, I don't like when people do that and it's if they're not, you know, it's not supposed to but it's like mostly they're just like lower smoke
I'll chill like, okay
Well, I mean it's like it's nice and calm. I don't think I don't think you know you're in trouble. We have a nice 15 people in chat
Do you have a cyber truck, Mr. Big Pies before curious?
I'm going to take a shot here. Cheers. Okay. Cheers
Missy
Nostrovia
I think that's Russian or something. Thank you
DJ, what are you talking about? You're why are you ready to be in chat? You're saying all these
weird things. How many people did you spend?
Gift in my rave gaze
How much did I spread the gifts? What does that mean?
Thank you. If you really want me to
No
Don't send me that clip. Don't don't send me that clip and leave me alone
I've not ever do that do it. I don't smoke we're talking about
No, strovia. Yes. I'm having a hard lemonade tonight
Ah cheers guys, oh
I hear beautiful guitar music
Is this Benson Boone?
Yeah what do you think?
I just learned this.
Nice.
It's terrified as the man stands to lose him
I fucked that up
This is you
Oh, I hope I don't lose you
Fucking shit, that's the best fucking part
That's fucking, hold on
I
Want you I need you
Is that is that Benson Boone
Is that Benson Boone or no, oh you left
I wanna ask some more questions.
Well, anyway, so guys, I got this new book,
it's a, because it's being loved,
oh, here it's back now on.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Well, thank you for the beautiful,
love singing a beautiful love song, man, I loved it.
Oh, yeah, could you hear it?
Yeah.
Cool, but I was thinking that is that Benson Boone or that's if I'm wrong or that yeah
I literally like that's like the second time I've ever played it
Like I just wanted it so I was like really confused about the thing
Yeah, I don't know if this big guys see this I mean obviously they're like some kind of
Stateness or something. I don't know. She's being very strange and putting me down in chat. So I'll I'll get him
Take care of it guys. I did get a new book. I got this. I mean, it's not a new book
It's like not just a notebook I've had but I was like I need a book for my show to like take notes through my show
And I want to put everyone's name in it and stuff and so
You'd like me to put your name in the book. Just let me know if I put your name in the book
Or I'll apologize to it on my own but
I'll put it if you're a modded stuff or you remember
So then I'll like look in the book somebody does something
I'll have a history and then I'll put a little stars next to your name and or I'll give you a little far any faces and
I even crossed out. Huh? You're gonna take a shot. Are you ready to do your shot? Yeah, let's do it.
Oh, yeah, I need to fix my patent. Let me see. We're getting that revenue pet. Let's take it.
Uh, I can't do a bad flip. You can't? No.
Well, it seems like, like, nowadays, it's like the younger generation, it seems like they can all do them without a problem, but
anybody over the age of, like,
25 is not able to. I don't know.
High pound patent.
Um, I'm gonna write your name in the book mr. Big pipes. I just have a
normal list of people
Now how do you know he's oh, oh come on Mojo Joe. He's first in the shots ridiculous. Have you ever watched this dream?
He literally bombeted me. Oh, that's that is not true
I think that's the same thing to say and please don't say this
No, I know I did not do that
Completely made up and this person is just trolley and so
Um, I'm pretty sure he smoked a
Once or twice when he was on hot huck is I please never
I don't smoke
Okay, so do we have to hear some interesting vocabulary though. I have like
All right. Oh, right. Oh, he's out of deep pipes. Okay. Yeah
Joke like I did that as a joke and if you like if you watch a clip
I actually like I smashed I smoke and eat out of it. Oh
Well, I did it because everyone's like you're smoke you're on meth
It's like I swear to God like I'm totally down to smoke meth and if I
Smoke meth in the future. I'll be like fuck. Yeah, I'm smoking meth motherfucker, but
Yeah, that was literally a joke like me being where she's smoking it when you're really
And they're like like what it like
There's like oh no, it's like I don't know. It's just some weird fucking stupid shit
But your hand was like Satan's Satan's stuff weren't you like
Like I wish you guys all doing that or be or something. I'm not I don't know. No, no
man, there's like
Give me a little Jacob gave me some Adderall actually and yeah, that's that's Matt
Yeah, well, I didn't I didn't take it but then he told me I was like, what did you what did you tell me?
I'm like, what did you give me? He's like I got this from vegan. Oh
The in-patriot I've heard so like I like I like somehow I got I got drugs from vegan through
Jacob that like I don't even I don't know that's what he said at least
She maybe she's maybe she's a secret the earth handler told him he's gonna stolen her pills
Well, I don't know was he around or did you just say she got from the Patriot?
I think I don't know but yeah, I think those those people like
You still are you?
Huh?
Are you still managing mod for being a Patriot? I think so I should man
Okay, so I wrote your name in my book. I'm gonna write mojo Joe's name
This guy. This is the good. This is like the good side of the book
Jojo
And so you're you're all I'm just gonna try to write down my mods names the people I know in chat
Mojo Mojo, do you want a burrow? Okay?
Mod
And who else is here, I see you don't know some of their name ads to the book. I mean, I wrote Pico Grammar
He's down to do hard stuff. I think he's down to do math like obviously if you ever watch his stream
Holy shit, I do just tweaking the fuck out
Um, who's Jacob?
Yeah, Jacob 14 or whatever people calm. Okay. He's kind of like a he does like a
He's been like he's streamed with a ton of people on IP to and now he does
What do you call it where you where you're like night crawler? He does a lot of that now
Well, I saw I saw I don't know if it's like I decided was there but I was watching this thing. It was on
Ice Poseidon's YouTube channel, which he doesn't you know, it's like he doesn't watch it
It's just extreme to YouTube face. He was in like a jail cell
But I think it was him with a bunch of like
Like there's some Asian guys and Hispanic guys and the black guys and they're all in this big jail cell and that's all their
All their shirts were off and like this they're like all thirsty and hot and like someone's
They have like a guard bringing on water and says first person to the or last person standing gets 50 grand or something
Time they've done that too like the same yeah, I mean they're making money off in the same stupid people watch
Oh, sorry, I shouldn't call him stupid the same people watch
Why did I watch it? I mean I like it looked at it for like two it was for you on a watchable for me
It was just like you know, I was like interested in they had their shirts off, but it was like I
Probably know I probably know like half the people on there. I could yeah
Like go fucking give me on the next one. I don't know
I don't know you should do it. You should do it. You can win 50 grand because the chances are
Like my in would be on who's on it
It's chicken Andy is there plus I stream snipe Kim ice besides girlfriend and then I know Benny Mack from like way way back
I met Benny Mac like in like 2019 for the first time
Any man, I don't know that is by just I'm Benny Brad
Yeah, any blocko Zealand dude or he's on okay, I mean, I think he's streams with ice beside
But yeah, like I'm sure those dudes would vouch for me early spinning back and chicken any knows who the fuck I am
Well, I think you're kind of well-known in the community. I don't know if I I think I did ask St.
about you one. I don't remember if I did ask about you. I think maybe I did ask about you or maybe just
many man or something. I do go to St. occasionally. He seems like he's doing really well. I think
he's still sober as a guy. The St. is still sober. He seems like he's a lot of time I saw. I just
haven't been on too much, but it's not like a... St. is going to be too happy with me, but...
I I didn't have maybe I had a I feel like I did have a fake saint in a chat one time like be like
Hey, I hope we can be cool or some shit, but I don't remember
Well, his name is st. 10 like st. 1 0
It's just that st. 10. It was probably him. I don't think people would like necessarily
Grow out of imitating him and doing that, but oh
Yeah, yeah screen with a geezer in Vegas. Yeah, or me and him we did like a eight-hour stream to go there
That was a lot of fun as I actually kind of like my first stream with like a affiliated person, I guess
Mm-hmm
Yeah, I still I mean I still haven't
Met up in IRL for anybody, but I would really love to I just can't go in here really people would have to come down
Spend some time with me and hang out on the pier. I don't think maybe yellow people are like a little
I'm afraid of me, but I'm supposed to be harmless because I was also treated. Oh, yeah, I see dream with
Yeah, okay
Yeah, so how's everyone doing a chat tonight more like I could have been at the compound like
the content compound
Mm-hmm. I could have been I could have had a till a spot or a chicken Andy spot back in the day because
Like me a till the noji geyser
First started screaming pretty much like together
Or like started like
Whatever figuring shit out and like networking and they were like the first people I met they had literally had like zero viewers
Like geezer would have like three or four people and he'd be like
3000-4000 people watching and he just be drinking beers at the at the office
which was a
Like a power thing next to a gas station in Vegas
Yeah, well
Yeah, I would love to see you in Vegas. Yeah, I'm gonna come. I think I've been invited to Vegas later this year, but I don't know
I'll go
It's really hard, you know expensive to travel or people talking about in chat. Yeah
The pipes. I'm rich. I
Was there pipes? Have you ever heard of mold mansion?
Who?
Mold mansion. Yeah
Yeah, okay. Yeah, actually, hey, yeah, I want to like give a call out to anyone in New York right now
my boy Jose Sanders
Another person I stream with like multiple times
Like he came over to my house and we got a hotel together on another stream for like two days and
He's in New York right now
He's in New Jersey or New York City. He's like in that area and you know, he's just like streaming like under a bridge
Someone helped him out with some clothes and a haircut today, which is cool. Oh
Yeah, Jose's a real one like he was living under a bridge and shit or like he just dreams
You have
Are you a borrow?
Did you like my dick pic?
You keep you keep never sending it to me
You sent you sent me a picture of a hot dog. I
Never saw anything. Where'd you send us you?
What are you doing so
Where my girl beta beta was here last night and
Um, she streamed to last night, you know, there's a little bit of drama, but we I think everything's cool. Oh
You don't get along with me right now. I don't know
No, I know I I I I do but it's like, you know, but last night like she's like, you know
she started like making fun of me and like
Like laughing at me and stuff and and then like then laughing when I was like kind of like being defensive and then
I don't think that makes me and and then it's like as though then we have kind of like we're friends. Yeah, we're friends again. Yeah, she's super cool. She's very cool. I think I just like, you know, I don't want to I hate fighting with people. It's like a comfortable and I hate like I always regret.
I say something dumb and I I'm not perfect, but it's like I just like some of the fights I like I don't I don't know what I did.
Oh, yeah, she is okay. Well, yeah
I'll let women think or women are you know, there's I think they're closer to perfection than maybe men, but
Yeah, I think women are you know
We're we're very cool, you know, they stare I think they're goddesses so
You want Marybita or your marriage
My problem. Oh, I mean, I'm not gonna marry you either, but
That's a weird question
Yeah, she's perfect. I mean, it's like if you actually idealize a woman that
Unperfect, I don't want something that's perfect. I want somebody like me bro. That makes mistakes as human
Well, I mean, but I think that's everybody and even people that even people think they are perfect
Or they are close to perfect ever. We know we're still no we're still all human beings and
You know, you have that in common
But I don't like to think I'm better than anybody else or you know, I just like to think we're all we're all equals human beings
So, yeah, CG3. Yeah, I know my eyes are going back to you Mojo Joe. Yeah, so, you know big pipes
Big pipes over
Oh, yeah. Is that the guy that lives in his dad's basement in a bed that's like a BMW or something?
I don't know. Is that true, Mr. Big Pets?
Probably no. Not accurate, but I think you're on the right track.
Yeah, I know what that is and well, I mean you live in your parents basement and you live in a your bed is like a
The shape of a BMW or a car
Yeah, I sleep in a race car. Oh my gosh
They make race car best for results
I got nothing I people criticize this guy I don't know him
Me so he's been a gentleman with me. Yeah, I think I think what's his face?
I don't even know his name that guy try to poke your eyes out. I forgot his name
They that's what I remember
Say, yeah, they say you try to poke your eyes out or something. Yeah. Oh god my eyes
That's what I remember about you and besides the fact that you have a
Car size bed in your parent's basement. That's right. Yeah, likely like to each other
Two very important things. I'm immune to eye gouges and sex trafficking
Well
Just because he never is sex traffic doesn't mean I mean, I mean
What do you think they were doing?
This is the problem with psyching.
I know, I know.
The problem with psyching.
You excuse.
Generate behavior based on how you you're attracted to somebody
Listen if this motherfucker look like the elephant man, you'd be fucking criticizing what the fuck he done
Well, I'm
I'm really nice to people, but you know
No, but he I mean he kind of like as a resemblance help a man, but I mean
So it's a bit of a mess, you know Stig, Stig, I think Stig said he's coming out of the closet tonight guy
I mean, I don't know. He's thinking, well, he said he's not gay, but then he seemed very, very confused
Every gay you're straight
And then he said he was taking like he said he was driving an RV to California and and I'm having sex with 300 glow
But I don't I don't know but I don't know people will just will say the opposite thing. I'm like, well, it's true
I don't know
Sometimes I don't know but who is this guy? That's Alvaro and then we have mr. Big Pie Smith. Yeah, the king's arrived
Alvaro. Yeah. Oh, yes great men of gossip is here. I'm all I think they say they know you
I see this but it's me Alvaro see oh it's it's great man of gospel but yeah I like
that guy he's a good guy okay and what's up with you know Joseph Merrick with
anything else yeah he had I know I know yeah Mojo Jo that's a show they made a
movie they also made a movie called mask it's kind of loosely based on that but
maybe also true story and share and that's a guy in it but he was a horrific
Hey, most interesting man in the world
You know, you know all the corpse of the elephant man was Michael Jackson
It was oh you own the corpse. Yeah, I know I think that maybe that was an urban legend
But maybe he owe the bones of the elephant man. Yeah, they would say that
Well, if anyone can buy them was him or if anyone booed by those having me he bought all kind of ridiculous things
Yeah, you might be able to buy bones though, but I don't know about the legality of like, you know, John Merrick's bones, but
Did you sell people's hand donate their skeletons or bodies for medical research and
I guess I think you're saying you're saying if you look if if mr. Big Pipe's really the elephant man
I wouldn't I would criticize. Yeah, I did say the hell. Sorry. Yeah
Well, I would I wouldn't I mean I think I could I don't I don't really judge based on looks that that mushroom, you know
But uh, I also I don't think I don't have that bias for men or women, but maybe I am dignitized sometimes
I don't I don't think I gotta hear it. I don't think I'm a big person's type
Here's a wonderful that movie. Yeah
Mr. Big Pipe's how old are you again?
I'm almost 40. Hold on. I got to meet this for a sec though. Okay. What happened?
He's gonna have a new person. I got a question. Somebody like him that's like 40 or almost 40 and I
Don't know bro. Like I just I don't know him. I just assumed that he
Just lives off his parents. It's okay to live with your parents
But it's a different thing to live with your parents and not your parents
Well, I think he like said that I think so or he said or somebody said that you know
He's just on the property his own trailer and then
He doesn't pay rent for you. It's not his own to be a pain not because there's always a tax property
I know that that's like a word that is
Is my microphone too low or what I hear you
Oh, you're a mute you're a mute for a second. Do you do do share it? No, I got it. Okay. Oh check
Output
It was like it like barely showed up when I just played it or it's trying to play a song earlier
You were let's see. Yeah, Dan CB. It was obviously be up at CB in my book. I'll put
New videos in the channel. Let's see. It barely
Do I go to my I'm gonna put you in my book. Uh, let's all borrow. I'm gonna put your name in my book stereo audio
Oh, let me mute it again. Oh, yeah, oh you left, huh?
Well, I see be here. No, no, I'll borrow it
but see if I put your name in my book and uh
Maybe I'll put the name of a book. Let me know. I'll put it in there
I'm writing a book. Can you hear my guitar?
Yes
Yeah, I was gonna quit with the panty-droppers, but I think that fucking beautiful things song is kind of a panty-dropper
Well, yeah, did you really chat drop their panties? I
Think that I think that is a PNC dropper song
If they're not wearing panties
Not wearing panties that they're
They're
Upskidled their dress flies up or something. I don't know. You're busy. You're interesting. You're the most interesting
It's like cross your legs cross your legs ladies
Yeah
Yeah, mr. Rappers are you into like you're to cunnilingus
Performing cunnilingus to perform that
Depends
Kind of like it's the vagina right where we need it. Yeah, or am I getting it wrong?
That kind of lingus was like oral sex on a woman
That's right. Let's say that I'm gonna say eating pussy, but you're the other way
You said that's kind of like gays fuck like I say I I never have done it. I've never done it. I can tell
Well, yep, so that obvious
I'm gonna play a song. I hope the guitar works
Cuz it's not like it didn't work
I'm gonna turn the echo cancellation off. I'm gonna mute the thing. This one's called...
Something the way she looks.
Okay, what was your show?
I gotta start it.
I didn't have a dime, but I always had a wish
I always had high hopes
I had different high hopes for a living
I didn't know a thing, but I always had a fear
I was gonna be that woman
I always had high hopes
I said, I'll fulfill the promise
I'm a first destiny, back in the days we wanted everything, wanted everything
I'm sick of talking about these things about your history
But I don't show why I'm just squeezing victory
Every day we wanted everything, we wanted everything
I'm sick, don't give up, it's a little complicated
No love, and I had to see you with
Had to have a high life, just for a living
Sure both stars, but I couldn't make it
Didn't have a time, but I always had a vision
Always had to have eyes
Thank you
Whoa! Wonderful! How are you?
That's that's Lola most I had it. It's the big pipes. Did Lola you like mr. Big Pipes music?
I think she likes you
Here you go, babe. It doesn't make me feel good
No, she likes no, she likes you
No, she likes you she has RBF like you know, but
I swear, I promise she does like you. I remember watching Nirvana and MTV in plug in Italy. You got the video
I've ever seen that series with classic performances of
sitting and dreaming
Yeah, I'm not like them but I can't pretend very oh very cool pipes. Yeah, Mojo Joe likes it
Mojo Joe's in
Marriott England
Hello, thank you. I'm yeah, I'm playing a guitar
I
Got I know another pretty one. I like this song
I'm gonna play as anybody's panties panties come down when you played that
We need some feedback
This should go on there.
Funny, funny love
Like my lady mr. Big Pies
That was a song. Hey, it's a lady
Could you hear it? Yeah, it was what was wonderful. We love this one
Fuck yeah
Yeah, it's probably my favorite one of my favorites for sure my favorite
I just got this on team with this light. I don't think it's the light around me. Oh, that's cool
Nice it and look but like it goes to different a world borealis
Just like this are
Hold on. Let me grab another chaser. Okay. Hey, can you do it so that it fades? Oh, I like that one where it's like green and red
Can you do so that it transitions like not like a blinking it just kind of like fades in each one
I don't have to test the remote out because like my lights do the thing like they strobe like that
But I like them when they like they'll fade the transition to I just don't know. I'm not sure but okay
I like in terms of brightness. I guess you got to hit like a certain combo. Yeah
Oh, you can do it. It seems like you got the same like chip in there
But you got to hit like one of them. You got to hit the one and then hit the other
Like hit the transition then hit the fade. I hit fade and then transition or whatever
Turn off
Like lighting I don't know I like this one. I was I like that one. I don't like this
I don't like to blink. I just like it like this. Yeah, I like it changing
But I think it can fade it can like fade. Oh, but I'm gonna grab another chase. Okay. Oh
This is I found a seven button. Oh, that's it. Oh, there's a seven color. Me too. Is it the same one as that one?
Yeah, there's the same as that one
If you need to delete that and I can go like that. Oh
You guys think that's your favorite color guys blue pretty cool
You guys
Unfortunately
Because they look cool. I'm getting for the proclamation of this child. That's that she she's a friend cvn if they understand me
They can survive. I'm going to let them
Leave maybe
So what's that for me? Where's your cut? What do you guys are you guys making illegal illegal deals my child? What's going on?
Yeah
Maybe yeah, is there anyone else with their name in my book or any suggestion for pages within this book?
Like what should I think is there should there be a like a category of pages, right? You know
What?
Which?
Well, I don't know that the chat seems to be in like a world of error. I don't even know what they're talking about
I just gotta figure out like what the right key is for each one, so I just wing it
And I like, you know, like falsetto, I don't know if my falsetto sounds all that good, I'm like, it's kind of blue.
But, like, I don't know what sounds good, and trying to make it sound good, like, it just takes a lot of like-
It sounded good.
Especially for you know, probably you probably just think you know learn just learned it recently or you learn it recently or with that
Without the other song or is it maybe I'm amazed I learned like
three days ago
But I mean that doesn't mean a lot like that like
But yeah, it's like oh no, I mean, you know
I literally learned like an hour ago me like an hour and a half
Yeah, well, I mean I think I could think it's been a week trying to learn and I would not be able to reproduce
Like if you have no experience I would take it years like five years
Five years. Yeah, if I just take years
Alright if you know alright to play it that well as I did
Want to say like probably like shit. Yeah, maybe maybe five years
Maybe like two years would be incredible to sing and play
Like and they're not easy chords. I mean, you know
I'd say five years at least
And that's like hardcore practice
Now no, maybe you can do it in like three. I just saw you think it'd be hard for someone to like learn how to
You'd you'd have to start off singing and playing at the same time
That's the best I can do but see I can kind of sing but I I can't sing that great but I can
At least it doesn't sound bad to me like something
I don't think I could ever
Yeah, you were well
Yeah, Lucy did you know do you know any ABBA songs?
You can sing dancing queen that's her to the Friday night the lights are low. Oh, I need to take that my eyes one
It's Friday night and the lights are low
Looking out for a place to go
Oh, and I'm not music get in this week. You're in the mood for a dance. And when you get the chance, you are a dancing queen. Will has been, oh my god, I don't know what you guys are talking about. You guys are, you guys all know each other from somewhere else, I think. Hey, JT. Hey, B Bummer.
There's one of the Beatles, but what is he like actually like the first vocalist ever is
The most interesting story about public heart news that he was friends with Michael Jackson
He had a personal friendship with him. And then
Yeah, well, he told Michael Jackson. He's like, you know what the best way to make money in music industry is to own the music and
And so he's told the owners of the catalog, you know, I just don't know catalog
It's that's great advice. Thank you. And then uh, and then all of a sudden he heard he'd been out bid for the Beatles catalog by Michael Jackson
And Michael Jackson was now the owner of the Beatles catalog and he was not quite happy with it
And then Michael Jackson called us it was
I mean, I'm not gonna like I don't know. I can't relate to the fucker like
Adam McClaren F1 and shit like after that like five years after that he had it like the most expensive car in the world
He's a billionaire
Hey, nobody well Michael's daddy Mike Michael's dad was the Richard of Paul McCartney though and Michael's dad was the stories
Oh, yeah, Michael. He owned the Beatles catalog. He bought the Beatles catalogs were under Paul McCartney's nose
before the Beatles catalog when I worked at a
Like yeah, like every place I've worked at that's owned by Amazon. They play
Beatles and like link 182 in Michael Jackson
I think Amazon's in on it at this point
Amazon oh yeah, yeah, sure the Amazons are
Dan's you can army see be more. Yeah, I am with the Jan. Hey, you should celebrity
Is that you think that you you that you they keep out of me. Is that home? Who's the picture home?
I don't know if I like how my fault set us
Gotta turn you down
And you get my headphones, okay?
I could almost like I can put my v-tube. I made a v-tube thing
Huh, I can put that up here on VC face
Head on up. Oh shit. Oh is that gonna work?
I don't see anything, but no, all right. I'll put it back
I mean it looks better than that, but it's fine. Okay. Yeah, I didn't I just weren't no worries coming on
So you have I don't have the camera on I'll just I'll just I'll just have myself
Very nice night, you see the ambiance of the overall borealist guys
People on tender waiting. Yep one match. Oh, it's your birthday JC. Happy birthday JC. I'm sorry. I forgot
Happy birthday Gemini
It's a good day. You're right on the summer stalls. This is your birthday right here. My dad's birthday
Let's go back to
Terrified as the moon stands to lose you
Ah, that's where it's gotta jump
Please stay
I want you, I need you, oh god
Don't take
Oh, yes, yeah
Hey, I'm trying to scream, huh?
I'm sorry
I'm cracking my voice
I'm trying to scream
I'm done, I'm done
I gotta scream, huh?
That's fucking killer, though
I love that shit
Like, it makes me, like
You want to come?
No
Even a noise that's not kind of like you may swim in fucking like like
Like chop a fucking block of wooden half or some shit. Oh
Well, it's kind of like you just make you want to drop your panties or no
No
If you could sense like the testosterone like
I'm scooting the pheromones from my fucking pores like
Like fucking in heat you do that your street hormones
What
Like since the fucking pheromones if you're around me
I don't know if I like it this guy smells like fucking
Like
Something something good something sexual
Well, yeah, I wonder this, you know, I don't know how, you know, I know pheromones are a natural thing and like, you know
People have them. I just don't know how there's some
Colognes that have them in them too. I just don't know that they work
But you guys know that even like most colognes like, you know, musk and stuff
They're all like musk is like from like the anal gland or sweat glands of a muskrat and
so in all these
Fragrances are actually like these
excretions from different wild animals and so they are they are a type of for
pheromone shoe and human beings do have reactions to these animal excretions
okay so you want to you want another course it's so good oh my gosh what's
outside is the one I had a motorcycle
Where it will
Yeah, my neighbor's on a motorcycle
Yeah, so what are you eating I guess?
Hi, babe. I'm thinking about going out to get something but I
Get mad I'm gossiped
I'm gonna leave a Yuba
I undertake her
Maybe
I mean I have a couple hours to go out still but I'm really not like
Trying to do that
Any you like you go
Okay
I'd totally got I used to know that song years ago
I gotta look at the courts
Okay, so what's on the menu tonight, let's see hi tricks
They have they have the offers
uh-oh here we go
Let me fucking figure out the chords.
Oh, okay. I gotta do them up top.
Um, should I go with...
C-shirt.
wait and psyche quit talking psyche you can you can talk actually I gotta figure
this out okay I'm lost okay well I'm just looking I'm just looking at the menu
I'll grow up right now I don't have a step and then
I'm up on the capo so I gotta kind of do a little thinking
okay okay I'll talk to the chat how are we doing chat
so I'm just looking at this
There's anything I want right now. Let's see. They have a mr. Beasprill. I don't look really good looks terrible kind of
Let's see
Rebel roosters. Oh ruby. Oh, that's not that good. I
Like it nice
Like a good deal though
Take out these deals four dollars off 20 dollars occasion see food. Okay. That's not good. That's good
But I need someone has a coffee though
Hi CB. How's everyone doing guys? Not too bad, but how about yourself? Oh, I'm pretty good. I'm pretty good
Looking up some
Possibilities for food. I'll just go to the subway. I forgot what their their specialist today though
Yeah subway has these these nachos and they look really good because they're Doritos nachos
And I love like the Doritos tacos and Taco Bell and stuff
As it reaches notches, they weren't very good in some way, but
some stuff is
So yeah, I'm not seeing anything I want there. So maybe I'll just go to the whole foods a little later
Or maybe I'll be hungry at 10. The fear of being irrelevant is strong with the old man
Speaking of seafood, I'm making a steamer pot right now. That sounds good
I didn't have like a few shrimp tacos and then I fish tacos and I had this
Really amazing grilled corn. They served on there
They just like they slightly kind of cut up a corn into like quarters like a piece of corn
they grill it and butter and
And came in the spicy seasonings. It's really good
Hey fish earlier
I'm a big fan of fish, especially now that I live by the pier. They got the best the most fresh fish in the world
This is actually the world's largest seafood market is right here
Just minutes away
Definitely I'm gonna I want to try it other stuff there, but most a lot of stuff there is very expensive
It's like over a hundred dollars and the people who get these big trays be a nice date
It's a big big a big trays needed there
All this seafood and lobsters and all kinds of stuff right meow
How's everyone doing in chat? Oh, it's been a little quiet tonight. I don't know you guys are still having fun with me
I know it'll be the show will always be different. It will always be different things happening, you know, I
kind of
Roller coaster life, so
I'll always have new things come going on, but you know sometimes
Make it a little slow, but I appreciate you guys being here. I know there's a lot of streamers out there
And I appreciate you spending time with me. Now you want ice cream and another
Beer he's gonna be begging for his neck. Oh, I don't know. Yeah, you guys are talking about your own stuff
I guess you guys are all friends. That's pretty cool though
Not cool cool it is
That last night it's like your smoke. I mean, it's just like so
I'm so cool.
I'm a professional.
So what is subway service?
So on Friday, subway serves,
I don't know where I have to look at them.
I can once walk across the street to there.
It's called a subway daily deal.
Okay, so today it's going to be
Okay, here it is. Okay, it says Friday's are
Oh, I can get a tuna melt that sounds good. I had one last time was really good
Oh, it's like no, it's a tuna sandwich, but I have to make it as a tuna melt
It was yummy
Oh shrimp you're gonna pass a bill to the mix on local shrimp, too
Yeah, good times is on tonight trying to lecture me about you. So you don't even know what a troll is
And he's like, you know trolls. There's gonna be some that are some that are gonna be crazy and then there's some that are gonna
Attack you I know
And he said I have some tell you and they hung up on me
Yeah, that's just and guys I have so much more to show you on the show, too
I have so many decks. I have so many more readings to do. I have so many books to show you and interesting things
I've brought out yet. I have a lot of stuff, you know, I need to wait to get organized first and
but now I feel like
Feel like I got a show so I
Need to work on
Organizing it better. I'll probably stream a little you know less hours without I wasn't going really hard trying to
Get established, but it's going at a good pace
Hey, JT. Yeah, so I guess mr. Bigpipes is working on his guitar and
Yeah, so I've watched some good readings though
I like to watch it, you know occasionally I watch other terror readers and you know
I haven't watched any readings in a while
So it's always good to also get a break from doing readings to like, you know, you don't want to get too many
There's so because there's every everything is out there. We kind of left them. I'm trying to chill. Let's take another shot
Okay, you know
Yeah, I know I know Gianna and I am new and he hasn't probably been at it more years, but it's like
He's like he's he was talking to me like I was like some idiot
Just up the train
He's there without a shirt on telling me
What is and I think I know I'm running actually playing I'm writing a book about trolls and trolly and I
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
There's probably like 5% of people that have YouTube actually have subscribers. Yeah
Yeah, I'm telling you like you see what like I I
Had the proven path like you can chill and still get like everything you could ever want
Mm-hmm from YouTube
Yeah
Well, I think I think we have me a lot of my morals like yeah, I'm a real person like what you see like this is the IRL experience
No, I I agree. I'm real too as real as I can be and you know, I've been in a very
unselfconscious moments where I was just
I've got a lot of confidence doing the show actually, but I would say what really helped me was doing panels
And I think mr. Big Pipe's if you got out on more panels and like you know said hey
Can you perform a song and then you know I think people would like would come and say hi you
Well, if you if you want to build your you know your chat audience
Hey, you like it like it this way
But uh, yeah
Well, yeah, because I mean this thing I just do just you're on a panel just say hi to ruin and do a song and then
I just say hey check out my are you live sure?
So that's how I mean
99% of the fucking people you're pretty much the only person that doesn't kick me and spurge out if I play music or like
Have any sort of fucking intelligence or time
Yeah, well, some people are concerned about live music or it's just not part of their show, but
Well, you know, like, I don't know. It's like I
Don't mean it's like I mean, I wouldn't taro in cities
But I'm saying I wouldn't taro into these things some chat
They were very hostile to taro and I would just go in there and just like, you know
Some people would be mean to me and like it was and some people would say hey, I want a taro reading and then I
Usually they would that person would like it and then they maybe they're probably in the chat right my chat right now
I have a lot of it. Yeah
Sounds pretty that is pretty
It could be an a harmonica
Let's try that
There's a D. Oh
That was the E. Oh my god. I thought that was the D. It was the E
I think that was the issue. I was looking for the D. I
Think psych is looking for the D, too. Oh
My gosh
Well, this was the D I was looking for
I'm gonna get that last one.
Did you feel the D?
Kind of felt the D, right?
I felt your D.
Oh, I'm sorry. That was inappropriate.
C-sharp 7.
Um, does somebody look at the chords real quick?
Oh, that's weird.
Cat hair.
7 9 10.
It sounds like jazzy at the 7th.
Another one is what?
Different shape.
9th 10th.
Again, everybody.
let me look at it from a nine bar and pull off to 11
thing that's out of the world i'll move to the beat of this one jump
I tried playing it through. I was trying to get the little like fucking fancy
Uh, have sherpas of them. I almost had it. Oh, it's flat there
I didn't have it like that
Oh, shit! Hey, verse!
Okay, your favorite.
C-sharp 7. Which one is it?
I wouldn't know.
Baby, I'm amazed.
oh my god that's it
you got to drop down
7-5 what the fuck
god damn
but that sounds fucking sweet
too easy
i mean i think you're right, so someone's saying people are infiltrating my stream, like
talking about the c, f, what is that the
that was
discord
this one
There's like you yeah, I'm here. Very good. I'm trying to play
I'm trying to learn hook my boot the blue's travelers
There's some course we know see
Sharp minor seven I
Don't know what's going on
But it needs to go higher let's go nine
Yeah drops down
7-5
That's it. It's gonna do that. Very good. Well awesome
I like smooth that out a little bit, but that's the tricky part.
Okay
He was here
I'll do another shot
Okay, I gotta go live at some point. Am I going live? Okay?
Z-30 now, maybe it's later where you are. Yeah, I probably go live at like
Nine no one's getting trash. Well, sorry. Yeah, sorry. I think it's already now over there
No, it's like 1030 where I'll go live in 30 minutes bucket. Okay
You can go live and I'll go to subway well
Let's have a great night. Hey, hey, can you get me? What do you mean? I would have tricks and now it now what I mean
Oh, thank you, JC. Thank you, JC. It's even on panel. No, this is mr. Big Pipes on panel
It's also the channel you can just look up mr. Big Pipes
That's one of the chords, huh? I don't need to get fancy with them
Let's have sure we're having a good night. I kept saying it's Saturday night
My days all screwed up
Yeah, my roommate in college played the guitar, and so I mean, he's nearing guitars.
Wait, uh, Will DiCinaccio is getting, I don't know the name, Will, Will DiCinaccio?
Will Dick? Oh.
That's like the fancy one. I want the simple one for a C-sharp 7. Is that my third for it?
What is the beauty contest?
I don't know. Like honestly, I never thought like I was that much of a looker, but like I've always like
I've always fucking dated the house tricks. I've like anyone ever known dude
Nice if you're you're very good-looking. I yeah, I think I don't know who they're
Chances to talk about all kinds of weird shit like they're gone off the
I don't even know how to chat anymore. I have a low self-esteem like I really do and then it's like
Now I'm asking myself like
These fucking chicks are so fucking hot like they're like the hottest chicks ever
It's like I saw the chick like I was like oh my god
And so how's chick ever and then I'm like fuck on her and shit
Yeah, they've had loads of the sea you probably wouldn't be confident up to even talk to them
So it's like you obviously have some kind of confidence
Yeah, I mean that's like a given like, you know, I'm a giant penis
I mean, it's not like a giant, but it's pretty nice
It's 99 percent. Oh, I'm not going to lie. It's almost nine inches long.
It's closer to eight and a half. Eight and a half, okay.
Well, you can always take eight and a half and just ramp it up.
A healthy night.
Anybody, did everyone know that Mr. Bigpipes has a nine inch wiener?
But there's a lot of surface area. Oh,
it's girthy.
Yeah, totally.
I don't know. It's like, if I had that thing strong in my face, I've seen the reactions.
I just like turning around with a bone. It's like, what the, like, how do you fucking smack in the face with like, something that's going to hurt?
Yeah, I don't think I've ever been slapped in the face for the dick anybody. I do have my own streams. Oh, yeah
Where's it had it?
Where's here? What's where you read it? I don't think I've ever seen read it as we're here before but they know Alex
I know me. I guess hi. Hey. Hey, they're spoke to you. Thank you. Oh, thank you. Thank you so much
Yes, it is here with the intro
it's a big part of the maze that you're playing this song
i'm trying i'm trying to like do it together
no i don't i don't know you can
on this like nine and i'm playing acoustic this one it's hard to play
you gotta drop it down
I don't know how to play F sharp minor 7, I can really figure it out, but is it really
all barred?
I would know why is that you let are you homosexual?
Homosexual star for other people's
What do you have a stop screen? I'm an artist figure it out Dork
And then I need the C-sharp seven
Be sharp
Uh, I don't like sauce. It's great. It is still gay pride month for another 10 days. It'd be nice to me. Okay. Yeah, it's gay pride
Hey, there's monkey, okay, oh
Yeah, I don't talk about you that they're talking about somebody in the chat. I don't I don't know this has
very uh
Why can't you successfully can't have your own losers are so interesting
Oh, that might work, it was a cheat.
I did, I did solo streams for like, probably four months, then I used to do panels, I did
I found the cheat. Let's take a shot, bitches. Okay. Hold on. I got it. I got put the can. You in you in fucking truck
You got to kill this fucker kill it kill motherfucker kill it motherfucker
Psyche Psyche give me a double take give me a double take. I'm gonna I'm pouring it. Listen. Okay. I
Bear
Come on. Give me another one. Give me another one Psyche. What do you want?
Another other chat of your fucking hard lemonade
Here yeah, I'm gonna do it. Hold on wait wait wait. I'm gonna fucking uncork my dr. Pepper
Breaking with me. Cheers. All right, let's drink up cheers
Okay, yeah, I don't mind you guys. Yeah, if you guys have any comments for the chat
I'd you like to be included in the conversation
But I don't know I don't listen to people. Hey Lenore. Have you seen Lenore guys? Hey Lenore come here
The reason going that's lately. She's been outside all the time. She runs it using darts around
Go back outside. Just in front of me howling
I gotta run this court, so just learn which ones were they this one is barred
I'm not four.
I've been like maybe I'm amazed for a little while.
I don't need tea, but then it's like kind of like nothing to do with my show or not because all this
It doesn't matter what I say
As long as I've seen
Looking for an action
It makes you feel I can feel
No
All right, bud.
Ah, yes, got it, it's a very good song.
I can't touch the drugs on it.
Just use this shit.
I prefer to.
Got it.
Yes, sir
Yeah, you were fine
Hey guys, there's no there's no there's no being there's no being on my on my hood in my
Go back to your own territory, you're the you're the you're the you're the shark from the jets
I forgot it, but I'm just kidding, it's a show.
CT, hi, got you.
I don't know, it's like a little,
cause a little quieter night, little old man finally,
you know, just during the conversation,
I don't know what's going on in the chat.
You can have the conversation in the chat.
Some big pipes is serenading me right now, a little bit.
Flabbergasted so you had to the guys was I don't know. I don't know you people you guys are all new
Thank you, thank you JT
Help up my stream
Yeah, I'm doing marketing stuff when I'm kind of hungry right now
If he is then I'll just I'll have to kick all you guys out. No because my show
I have to start it back from the ground up I will
Boilers I don't know boilers
Alex got Alex who's got me all in my head. I guess I'm just kidding. I really don't care
But there's a lot of people that chat and never say hi to me and never introduce themselves never said anything
They're just here to chat with other people. It's kind of insulting
I'm the main attraction here me me me me. It's about me. Okay. It's about me. It's psyche
Did you think God has a channel though?
Did you think he has a channel? I think it's funky or great. Yeah, some guys. How are you guys?
So we're not going up on panel because I'm weighing out every romantic evening with chocolate cake. What do you do to the cake, Goddy?
This is an American pie situation or your goddamn
cake with a hot girl killer. What the fuck?
We should I just had to listen that back. I was like
This is good. How do you gotta get a wrench now? Oh, so you're like, it's what it's funny
It's funny. God is holding on to his wrench with a little a little tiny like it's spiders spiders thread
He knows he doesn't good guy, that's what you know got the guy. He's still he's behaving himself. I'm watching you Godie
Booping the cake
Oh my gosh, dude. I can bust that out anywhere and like anywhere I bust that out like it's gonna fucking like
blow the fucking pain
It's where to go. Yeah, I guess we can't I can't it'll be too much though be too much
There'll be too much sprinkler action in the shadow. I don't want the computer equipment to get wet
Okay
I don't want to stream rock. I want my own stream
We'll go do it. We'll do it. I want I will I will
Just gotta like why is pipes camera up?
I don't think it's camera
I came on here to like take a few shots and I ended up taking like seven or eight
Cheers, I haven't I have that effect on guys. They just they're like, what am I here?
You just pass it on my floor. It's good. His pipes are too big for the lens he uses. Yeah, like I could have taken a fake shot
It's a real one
Well, I mean we can't bear it. It's like you say you just 40 push-ups that time
And you did like 10 seconds and nobody saw and you know, I didn't do that
I've never done push-ups story, but there are videos of me doing 35 push-ups
No, you did but you did but you did up because your camera was like this your camera was off and then you're like
37 38
Yeah, and then we're like did you really do that?
It was literally like in one like like three seconds to a minute that you got to like 40. Yeah
I'm losing. Hey, but yeah, I can do I could probably do like I at least I could be 30 easy right now
Like but there's a video of me doing 35 on my channel. Well, okay. I want to check that out
I'm gonna watch that
Hey
Pipe's music reminds me of this. Okay. What is it? Someone tell me that what single post I can't
Okay, go ahead play a beautiful song
This one's a safety be back like years ago say go to always be like play Radiohead or some shit
Do I have it when you on page last time? It's a big pipes. That's how you aren't panel you page was here
Did they happen with you on page? It seemed like some chemistry
I don't know I mean she's a pretty girl like I'm sure there would
Like I don't know. She'd probably be the girl like I'd fucking be focused on if like I saw her
Well, she doesn't have a show I've been to her show
She has very page and wildflowers
She was live occasionally
There are regulars here.
Discord Brigade, Discord Brigade!
Oh, no.
Ma, if I, if I, Ma, Ma, if you guys got it,
can you just ban the Discord Brigade, please?
I can't take it anymore.
I have to, I have to figure out how to play guitar really quick.
Gotti!
Gotti, 99%? Oh, wow.
Well...
I got that 1%, I got that little 1%
Little
Little thing to say I'll do it and I'll get all the 99% back to you spunky on panel makes me miss it
God oh God he is the mod power going to your head, you know
You're for the disco parade. Oh, no, okay, so first of all
There's no disco parade here. Mr. Big Pipe is playing
Some bluegrass, maybe but it's not disco night. Okay second of all
Gotti
Got to call up your people or I'm about to I can't have you as a mod and then I'm saying oh
It's just referring to you. I have to give you an ego for this shit
So Gotti, why don't you just have fun being in the chat, okay?
These are gonna be too weird. Hey, Jamie
Do you need to we're gaudy can't take it
Play the clip of big pipe asking in his ass beat by that five six six hundred thirty pounds saint ten
I know since it's my sense of friend of mine. I love saying
Yes, Mr. Big Pipe sees playing he's gonna play one more song. It's okay. You're just called ball
Gotty no, don't I don't want you to try to figure it out. I can't figure out the one part
Yes
Because I'm listening here like I'll mute it. Okay
There is yeah, Jamie's here, Jamie's you know see Jamie's has a seniority of everybody
I know, I know, it's just, I'm just kidding, too.
Just, I know, I had to take away Gotti's key
to the office, I'm afraid he's gonna come in
and smother him with a pillow when I fall asleep.
I've already flashed your Tonka toy.
I was going to ask Stade to come on.
Yeah, but Prespaiz, but he's not streaming right now.
Yeah, I actually like, I'm Oliver's,
I'm not saying to come on, he said he would,
Supposed to happen he just never has but I'll ask him again
Yeah, he's he I mean he is a little bit, but he's also like very he's very very
Masculine side to him, but yeah, he's funny. He's funny. He's an interesting person. Mr. Big Pipes play
But you got it. I got it. I always give it back. I just you know, I think you like you let all these people in my office
With your key. I'm just kidding
We'll work it out. Got you. He's a werewolf. Yeah. Oh
Come on. Oh God, he's come on. I don't know how to hold it for a little bit
Yeah, I'm trying to figure for me
No, it's just it's just of course on the chat. It's fine
God he got God. Yeah, I've demoted you to the you're God. Can you give me can you give me some coffee coffee?
I'm pizza. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding
No
God he's like my secret agent like if I made him a mod that everyone would just know he's a mod there
And then they would they would know he's like listening for me. I need to I need everyone to think that he's on there
Got it
What are you seeing here? Asia man? Is that your romantic song?
Uh, this one's by the Radioheads.
It's kind of pretty.
Yes, please. I like it.
Actually, please. Love it.
Feel me. Well, I like Nicky guys. They see that's what it's like.
Go over there. Go over there and flex for me.
I'm just kidding. Hey.
It's better if Jamie just has the rent. I mean I just give women the power. They'll take care of things
Well green is a member icon. Oh god, he's a member
I
let's just let's just leave it there. It was fucking beautiful. I danced. I was.
It's beautiful. I think Jamie, Jamie Cowboys is applauding. Oh, I think Jamie Cowboys.
I really like, like, I like talking to her about her passion.
Just hearing something like it was real just like I appreciate
Someone talking about something that's real like that like a true passion
True passion
Well
Jamie watch out for this guy. Mr. Bigpipes is a charmer. He his music flows when his panties off apparently
Jamie
I drew the other picture of him in everything. Oh, I'll draw you. I'll go. I'll tell you got it in the book
And the JT
Guys when you all become the member you can all become the member game up to no no mod game become a member game
I'll subscribe or a member
There's a review right here. You see Marie
Where are you? You're here here?
It's soft
Well, no one's been here too. I don't think she was just here. I think she went out
There's an echo. Yeah, there's a little echo, Mr. Elk, we'll see if I can fix it all.
Is that better, guys?
They have fixed it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jamie. Everything's okay.
take a shameful evacuation my bladder really quick. Okay. I'll be over here. Okay.
Guys, we can't talk about him because he's right. He's right in his room. There's a chug in his
corner. I was kidding. No, he doesn't know. Yeah.
I think I think the modding my modding situation is just gone out of control and so I think we're gonna do like the less mods thing
they go forward but
You know money is money
It's like it's a thankless job anyway, but it doesn't pay it tastes terrible
I know I was a mod
You make a penny
My I think you did it. I think he's in the corner of his room. Oh, there's the door
He's in the corner of his room. I think he's a bucket or something in the corner, right job. Get to ask him
But we did have um, we didn't have the guy yasin. He was a little bit the other day and he had cleaned out his piss bottles
I think it's time for Taco Bell. Maybe I'm thinking I think the subway cuz I don't think it's Taco Bell
I don't have to go anywhere
This is a this is a big
Yeah, I know Robert. I know and then I saw because I saw scribbles like made the same mistake
I think other people make things like I didn't make a mistake by modding everybody because it was like
You know, there's just the same people in the chat at first, you know
But then like a lot other people came and I kept modding everybody and then it's and there's all these different gangs that are like
Fighting over wrenches. I don't even know what's going on. So I just have to like have my little he flirty. How are you?
I like that my little little wrench gang
I think everyone's good today
Yeah, well I'm sorry if you can just rip pipes is just evacuating his bladder. I think he's just
about to start his own stream, but
I want to say hi. I like the
You guys say hello to each other. Okay, so it's talk about oh what's talk about says what it says is free
Regular dragon fruit freeze
When I spend 20 so that's just like
It's not a greatest deal in terms of the book, okay
I'm laughing at those okay, let's see
Statement will have his two. I'm missing the chat. Let me see. Oh
He's oh, yes, I love stamina has a wrench. I don't know
It's like I just
Taco Bell is overpriced. Yeah, it is a little bit. Well, it's so and also so is uh, what happened?
There's haters there's no haters my chef
The love box in here shake shake shake
I'm just gonna shake
She's your team shake it off by Taylor Swift. Yes
Yeah, I can play it on. I like playing on banjo.
Let's do it.
I know it.
I gotta find the right harmonica.
Let's see.
How many harmonicas do you have?
Uh, like all of them really?
30 does have a rented thing. Let me see.
I have 1, 2, 3, 4, like I got like 5, 6 harmonicas in front of me.
6 harmonicas.
I'll use them all
Red Robin guys, that's pretty good red Robin red Robin for this. Oh, that's liberal officers
Okay, El Taras, that's a good Mexican restaurant
Donato's pizza
I'm not I'm sure you do but like to the door stop and shit like if I do this shit in real life
Like an idea
People fucking feel it and love it. Like it's a real thing
Yeah, I mean, I think you know, there's just like there's people are just kind of trolling you
I think they do appreciate your music and everyone loves the talented musician. So you go mr.
Big Pipes don't ever let anyone tell you
Anything else you just do you
That's a good message. Yeah
I'll take like half a shot here. No, I got a fucking
Okay, we'll do a final
our lemonade
If you play the harmonica with your what was your what? Hey, there's spunky
Cheers here
Put it on
Yeah, I think I think I'm gonna go with more to the Elisa and Emma
strategy with mods where it's just like I'll have like a few women that I know
The men are the men are unpredictable
I think I'm a good model. Is that the actual see no, it's not see
God is an unofficial mod
Yeah, it's a speaker. His wrench is like his little, his little concealed carry for his wrench, so don't use it.
I'll stay out to sleep. Nothing in my brain. That's what people say. That's what people say.
The argument is that I can make you stay. That's what people say. That's what people say.
But I think it's okay, I'm still, I'm still
But I got this music
And I'm not sure it's gonna be alright
Oh, okay
Oh, excuse me
Yeah, it's still there. It's still there to every video.
Every ten is there.
Oh god, he has a lockpick set. He has a lockpick set. There's no icon for it yet.
I love my love
Did you say hello my love? Yeah. Hello my little honey bunny
My little sugar tush
Yeah, like Bonnie Bonnie my sugar torch my little baby wavy
Oh
Yeah, mr. Big pass shake it off whoa
Hey
Mr. Big Pipe
Yo big pipes big pipes have a conversation
he does that, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he, he
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I love it.
Did you see the tag attack you
in? Where'd you tag me? Where'd
you tag me in the chat or where?
Okay
I'm gonna sub up. I don't even know why I haven't yet. Actually
I found them here. I met him here. Then I saw his video. He was doing push-ups. He was doing it to the Rocky sound
I went on a channel once and I saw him. He's like at concerts. He's like actually a musician
He tries he tries
I'm not gonna let it rock, but he's still gotta say sorry to beat him. Yeah
I did that man. Well, that's never he's never gonna do I mean
Hey another man
You're pretty he's gotta say to her to be you know, see this is why the cartel is scary
The same reason I can't go back to Columbia because some people don't let you go
30 years to pass
Yeah, it's a scary world we live in
Actually, what happened on my question is why so mad that they mentioned is taking like I heard a little bit of the combo earlier
But I was just you know
Exactly channel down we've been through so mad though when they finally got exposed I guess and do you know that is easy
You know remember on tvp that guy the reverend
That
There's some Mormon or a Protestant asshole of their called the Reverend and he sounds just like JT. Anyway
They're freaks and God fucked up the other day
Real quick, man. I catch some shit. He let us slip because they're all that oh right of course like
Right, I don't know what Christian shit or whatever they follow
But I guess I'm not normally right and and God slipped the other day
He was like, why would you get it to happen? God will you never get into happen like real quick like fucking around joking?
But they fuck up
They let it out here in there
Just like
Yeah, that's what I and say crazy shit because they want you should go man. You have to protect
But they gotta
Mm-hmm. I know and it does seem it does it does seem like it's uh, okay
So Billy bad it seems like it's some kind of anti-gay kind of campaign. I'm not sure I'm not sure then they yeah
Yeah, I think it's disgusting because I'm a straight guy. So to me in my mind talking of penis is disgusting, but
You know to gay people it's not and I'm not
But if you're crazy about a team going around judging the plan, they're like, who the fuck
are you, God?
And it makes sense that they're making God.
God, I haven't even selected dick in like a couple of years and so it's like I'm not even
You
Let's make it sense right now, you know, it's not cuz you're gay. We like you for you and that's that bro
This is like, you know these brigades or whatever
We're just guys, we're just us, friends, like souls, like, but you know, I wouldn't be like,
get away from me because you suck dick, or you'll be like, get away from me because you
touch pussy, or be like, easy, get away, like, no.
All the same at the end of the day everybody's the same even girls were all just women and guys
Which is all the same. You might have more money than me. You might have less money than me
We're all the same.
I came in with fucking knowledge tonight, people.
What the fuck is this nigga's script?
We're all the same because we're human beings,
but we are all different, and we all have our different
preferences, and we're allowed to have our opinions about
whatever we want to and think where we want.
It's just like, you know, we have to...
Hello!
the
Yeah, it was a bit wrong. It was called love me or leave me alone. It was a brand new billions in the 90s
You better love me or leave me alone
You know, love me or leave me over psyche. That's psyche's law. Love me or get better over which one?
I know JC and JC that's sarcastic that sarcasm that I mean, I always I mean I come on to it immediately like I mean, I'm I
Know I mean I like you know kind of like
Just so it's like, you know, let it be a reveal
And psyche they own a mountain of gayness I told
My brother was in my love of Tio
He bought a mountain in Texas and made it into a gay resort him and his husband
I went to his wedding
They're like extremely paid and they do drag
He his husband is a drag queen. He's like a comedy show drag queen. It's a big thing in the gay
You're like community
and he does drag queen shows every day at this nightclub and they stay like water mountain and stay sanctuary man my brother's gay
I hope you be alright today
I'm not with that bullshit
and I'm not gay
I'm the most not gay person
so if I can love and not judge and see that we're all the same
and love
you could joke around you got sense of humor
Yeah, exactly
He doesn't care
Everybody equally and I respect that
Back
I always like sake like you
Take is a good dude. I always like them man
Sake is a good dude. It's very
I could tolerate him big difference
Speed through it. I see through the fucking bottle. I've got the math. I big difference
Yo, where are you from my guy?
Are you from like one island over here? I'm around your block
Okay, some people talk like that other people don't
They wake up you're on a show
No, I'm not on the show. I'm unconscious
I'll be
Racist so what?
He has a good heart man, you can folks think he's a good dude with a good heart
He form bombs is where I don't have any soul
I
Don't have any soul and I'm a piece of shit and I'm going to hell and I'll be right back
Who said that?
Yeah, I got it Tony. Oh, sorry. Sorry. I was actually figured out last night that I'm I'm Tony and I'm doing this whole thing
I'm all the voices and most of the voices in the show
What Alice is the voice? How many people that I expose on TVP that way easy. Let me miss Rummy
You got a couple right got a couple wrong, but correct Alex and I admit that but when I hear you know I'm saying
Okay, got it. Just enjoy the show right enjoy the shit show. Wow when I was today, it's scary
Guy, you don't want you don't want a piece of this trust me. So it's a big hassle
I was today in the scary unconscious so I could had to leave it. I'll be back. Okay. Oh, yeah. Oh, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, Jamie. That was the only one here
Because it's always here
Look at this like you notice
Because they're not here. This is a shitty panel now. They're not here. You control me and Alex
Like numbers are dropping like a heat out
But it's fucking trolling one-on-one it's bringing panels down one on one
Can I try to get up here? I kind of trust your stupid ass first of all you go in
Right you go in and then you divide and you conquer right what they were trying to do I
Mean, it's the Trojan horse. There are the Trojan horse
It's problem reaction solution which it actually should be like you know it was problem reaction solution is like it should be you know
Problem
Sometimes when I'm really fucked up and I'll say dumb to a shit, but now I'm gonna be more careful of it because I don't do
That's the thing it's like if you like it's one thing it's like someone just is themselves and they say something
And that's that's fine. It's like if people that are and I'm not saying you guys got gaudium JT
I'm not saying you guys are doing this, but I'm saying
There are people that will try to like say things and then they'll like go try to like, you know, try to you take it down from something said, you know, and so that's why I'm
And I wouldn't think that but it just happens so much with so many people. Hold on.
I don't know.
Is
Okay, so the mr. Your name is Jan or Jari you just waved at the camera, so I know you're a real person, please Jan
Okay
No
Can I get a word in real quick before you bring these losers up the cop cock block me they're gonna cock block me
That's what these bitches
Yeah, I listened to the Alexander the other night and he's telling you guys a hundred percent
truth about these douchebags from
They call themselves CFF. They're chud friends forever chud fags. Whatever you want to call them
That's what they are. They're a crew of fucking doxing fucking assholes
JT Goddy CB
You got several of them infesting your room right now, but psych. I don't know yet
Is that what you like to be called psyche or psych? Yeah, you can tell me psyche
I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you, I told you
But he somehow knows all about these fuckers.
Yeah, he's telling you the truth, man.
I'm just like, you got exposed.
You got exposed.
Gadi's a piece of shit.
Gadi is a fucking mother fucking punk.
So is JT.
They're doxers.
They're fucking cloners.
They're fucking garbage.
Ziggy hangs out with them.
He's another douchebag that hangs out
with these motherfuckers.
Yeah.
They try to take shit over so what they try to do man. They ain't worth the fuck none of them will turn their cam on here
We are
Fuckers
Okay, yeah, and I appreciate, you know, I appreciate your perspective on it and, you know,
I still think this guy, yeah, because I know everything about these fucking cocksuckers,
these guys have dogs, they're a disabled kid, they fucking show their pictures, they came
up with a picture of me the other day, right, you shut them down, I saw you do that, yeah.
That's what they do. They use everybody's fucking pictures, but they're all fucking ugly fucking asses and they got you guys, right?
They're gonna fuck your room or you're not gonna have anybody here
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
All he does is talk shit with this can laughter. I can do it
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
You cannot fucking play a guitar. No, no, no shit. That's just a big part
I might be
what do you mean
there's another bitch involved here, you guys haven't even mentioned her, her name's Rusty
she's the bitch that runs it through
that was put on last night, Rusty
who is she?
you sound like a bored old man
well, well, no, no, he's laying the facts down
and he's laying facts because
God said he's bringing his whole crew over
You sound like a bored old man
That's just a bitch
They threw one rap even though it was night
They threw rap even though it was night
It was me, Ziggy
Like that time
Power and the DSC
You do what you do
Literally
You sound like
Who's backstage?
you're talking to me. I don't
Fucking
There's your 50
Jarl, your wife is from the 80s, stuck in the 90s.
Isn't that crazy?
Dick, say, at least you got a wife.
You got a wife, say, you were begging for a lady earlier.
You're a girlfriend.
Jarl, your girlfriend is literally from the 80s, stuck in the 90s.
That's scary.
Why does Joe keep touching his beard like it's a ton of blanket
He's a beautiful woman and I respect that
I don't know bro. I don't even trust Joe Wiggen right now
Psychic
He could be in on me
He doesn't have me
This is how crazy BS was though
Did she watch it? Do you want to open your mouth?
Yeah, open your mouth, the one with the crown
Open your mouth, cunt
Open your mouth
Open your mouth, bitch! We gotta put a cock in it!
Bits drop them drop them
you're gonna get blown bombs like you keep them crazy this is a good deal these motherfuckers
but it doesn't matter because as long as i keep learn whether it happens or not he's gonna learn
and get better every single time and so the enemy's getting exposed unraveled
Mommies you know you
I'm here to have gay sex with psyche
Anyway, this is their leader right here this bitch
What is your wiggin have a girl that looks like she's under his spell?
This is an appellate wiggin look at some old fucking hundred year old and he's got a girl
that looks like half normal.
That's crazy.
No, buddy.
Bro, you know, I'm like 40 right she's not 40. She's
What do you like the rest of you?
No, buddy.
What's the problem with you?
I Alexander you can't get
No, no
But this guy's 80
Why do you keep touching your feet like that? Are you okay?
I was in it. I didn't even like you.
What's that about? Are you jerking your feet or what the fuck is that about, bro?
Is that your control blanket?
Yo, take those glasses off because I can see the reflection in your computer.
Yo, you want acid right now? Are you on acid? Are you on drugs?
You're a dum-dum.
Yeah, that's a tweaking fucking coke ad right there
Oh god irritate you so much
Can you can that bitch take over wig and shows that she's 92 like you
Do you pay for her hair, daddy?
What's the tutorial about?
You straight on the corner so that bitch can have her hair?
The guy I have no idea what's going on.
I'm in the corner right now.
Alexandria, please.
No, no, no, pay your beard again.
Pay your beard again.
Alexandria, Alexandria, please. Be quiet, please.
Fuck nobody.
You're a nobody.
Quiet.
Is this your friend?
Is this your friend who wants to get fucked upstairs?
You in the basement?
You're a fucking nobody.
No, it's fine.
You and your bitch are nobody.
Nothing will always want a rockstar.
Oh, man, you're mad.
You don't want him to expose nothing yet, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let them talk, let
He's not married to her. He's not married to her. There's no record of a married marriage anywhere.
Marry me back Riverside County had to send me back $17 because I fucking had to pay for their marriage license. It doesn't exist
For the record, let's have a look at you
You want me to put a pickup? I'll put a goddamn pictures up there.
Put more pictures up there. Put them up there.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
We're gonna need a bigger...
No doxy please.
Liz, are you there? Liz, are you there?
Liz, are you there?
Hi.
I live
Use an old Patlaxis bitch over your list that bitch is from Australia. That's about a 90 year old mother
Don't think you need to be
Nobody
You keep calling me old, but you are too old for me.
This is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me, this is me
You are even too old for me, Wigan.
I'm way younger than you, way hotter than you,
and I'll be just not past you.
Just don't turn me with you, because she's been saying...
Fuck you
Listen to your voice. You're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you're such an old bitch, you
Why don't you buckers turn the cams on man, I'm too beautiful
I am fucking gorgeous
You'll fucking play to the chat now and get some for that bitch beside you.
You won't play to the chat and get some dick, won't you lads?
Watch your back off, that's what I want to do, I want you back off because no one wants you here bitch, no one wants you here bitch, go away, go away bitch
Rusty was too good for you, Rusty is too good for you and you've never got no for us
Why are you here because you want attention from everyone, don't you, George?
Don't you, you old truthless, wingy old man, all you do is bitch and bitch and bitch.
You're a fucking idiot. I was around us before you even came. You think you know everything.
We were here, Rusty and I were here way before you fuckhole.
fucking loser stuck in me. I
know. You know why? Cuz
Chase Gotti and JT.
Chase Gotti? No, I'm gonna kick out his ass
because he's a fucking fat ass fucking losing pig
just like you are. Okay?
I am fantastic.
I am a really, really good person.
And you have been whining and whining and whining for years.
You need help.
Okay?
I don't know. I don't know how
You are the biggest bitch out
here. You want to know why I'm
here? Because I was informed by
somebody that that fucking
punk JT came up here using my
picture the other day.
You're here, you're here because you both shaped us into a fish, and you want some of the jelly cake, I'm sure you'll need it.
I have to talk to my kids.
You're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here.
Yeah
That's why I told you, you dumb bitch.
No
Get that you are
It's like your mother abandoned you, you fucking son.
We can't win, and the reason Schussers can't win
is because they're losers, and you'll never win.
You got a fucking school-aged daughter, you retard.
Yeah
Dot you how the GM out
Did you fucking miss out on that, huh?
I'm very glad you're mad, aren't you?
But she even has the bracelet on her.
You're cocky.
You're abandoning your kids like your mom abandoned you.
You fucking whore.
You're abandoning my kids.
What are you talking about?
I got a shit on you.
Let's talk to you.
I'm talking to Dot.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking to Dot, who has four school-aged children, who
she abandoned her kids.
You're not abandoning a kid, you fucking moron.
Yeah
She abandoned her kids like a fucking dirty
Why do you give a fuck that JT put your picture up to make an excuse to come here, bitch?
What?
Yeah, JT was up here as far as I didn't know JT was up here before you.
I'm gonna drop on this channel, you fucking old cow, Liz.
Hey, you said my name up here, so I can...
Oh, an old cow. I am young compared to you, you really old fuck.
You are too old for me.
Whatever I know she was here. We know she's here. She was here before you
Sleeping actually, you know that now wise miss Liz up here miss Liz is Rusty's fucking lap dog is what this bitch is
We dominate you
I did not hear your bitch stream me out of the day, Wigan, Wigan, but I was told my name was in your mouth on your last stream.
Why are you bitching about me, bitch?
You were whinging about me and Gotti and JT the other day and probably rusty because you're infatuated with rusty.
You were talking shit on me.
the other day on your stream. So why the fuck am I here to say I don't know what's happening right now?
Why aren't you going and getting some park in Australia somewhere, fuckhead?
You're disgusting. You're an old
I don't talk to her like that man.
I don't talk to her like that.
You are dominated by me.
These are all the motherfuckers I own right here.
Dominated.
I'm nothing.
No, you are.
You are.
You're crying about Rusty, you're crying about Rusty, you're sadder than me, you're a lonely little fucking pot, that's just the beauty of your life, and you've got nothing going on, you're a weirdo.
Here's the thing you're ready lived your life. That's it for you
It's cut bro
It's cut for you, bro, you look like a fucking bro you look like Gandalf, bro. It's cut for you, bro
You'll do anything to get your happy ass
The crazy thing is that you're an old man
You're an old man, and you think you have me figure it out because you're an old man, but you're just an old loser
And I actually feel bad for you, and I hope to god that I don't end up like you
Because you think that being old means that you think you know shit
That's not the same thing
Figure it out
Which you fucking won't it's like that
We're out here and we're racist
Sister girlfriend, I believe in peace. I believe in peace
I believe in peace
That's his sister we've already fucking put it out there that motherfucking JT is fucking his sister. Well, it's his step sister
They're half sister. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't I don't want to get into like and I would do the same for you
I don't I don't want any kind of like
Accusations being on people and so I just uh, yeah, but it's interesting, you know, because I don't have been paying attention to the chat
but they're
Kind of going crazy in there
I don't know. I don't know.
And that motherfucking prick turned on me.
So, that's just another, uh, yeah, that's what we face in YouTube all the time.
We got all these wishy-washy douchebags everywhere.
Well, if you go look at their channels, they all dox, they have all-called cops on people.
They'll find out where he worked, they'll find out who your mom is through Facebook.
Okay, we already know about that.
We already know about that, okay?
The thing I'm addressing here is some fucking douchebag here who got jealous because I got a fucking girl.
See, I run into that all day long in here.
with all these motherfucking
incels, you know, and they
come in here because you put
these chicks up here with those
filters on and we've looked at
a few. They don't look like
that guys. They don't look like
that. Okay. Those are beautiful
filters. Those girls look pretty
but all these fucking queers are
in here right now. Gotti, JT,
Boil. These guys think they're
going to get lucky. You know,
they think they're going to get
I'm not coming back here. I don't intend to come back here
I told you when I came up here to let me get my save before those fuckers jumped up there and start cock-blocking me
Which I did on any stream I go to I generally don't go to streams or up on panels
This is a very rare occurrence and I came here to help you with these fuckers
But you know what? I'm gonna let them take over your room because that's what they're gonna do. They are going to
they've already taken over your room. Look at it. It's all them, dude. And what the guy was saying
before is you used to have more people in there and these people are gonna fucking destroy your
room because nobody likes them. Nobody wants to hear their shit. All they do is docks, talk goss
up on people, fucking fuck with people and none of them will turn their cam on. And nobody likes
these fucking creeps. Nobody does.
And all they do is bag on us because I tell the truth man. I'm a Christian. So is Alicia here
I understand you probably not but that's not the problem
You know the problem is I tell the truth where I find it and nothing hurts a motherfucker worse than you to ban
That fucking truth and that's what all these douchebags are
They're all pieces of shit and they all want something that what they want look man
They came in and attacked me in elder verse where I come from skull elder verse. I don't know if you hear about it
So a lot of IP two people went over there a lot of Aldi people
Q a bunch of other fucking people. Anyway, I ran their fucking ass out of there
I have destroyed these motherfuckers over there. They tried to get into my stream
They tried to get into JC stream
They've tried to get in all of our fucking strings that everybody's kicked their fucking ass out
Except for this one
But let go I say you dropped a troop bomb
We were saying this for a couple days on him and we pointed it out
But you know like I like even myself I got to learn I got to learn by my own I got to learn for myself
So
Let me ask you a question. How do you know this is not easy. Oh
Me and Alex been working on it when we come to the stream we were watching we've been watching
No, how can you possibly know all that shit you put out there unless you were watching our streams now?
We wasn't somebody else was and put us on see okay. I know who she is
Thank you. No, she know nothing. I'm just saying it's just I know
I'm not part of a team trust me. I'm not part of a team of teams like I don't know what you're talking about
Have I let me check now. I'm not trying to get anything dude. I just know about it. All right
All the evidence I know where you got everybody. It's all I'm saying, but it's the truth
So what you're putting out is the truth about these motherfuckers here
Do you notice Rusty wasn't even in chat or on the panel?
Now you know what, JT, you little punk ass bitch,
while you're down there, while you were mouthing off to me,
I wasn't gonna do this to you.
Because I don't want you around JT.
I want you to find a new home, bitch.
I want you to get the fuck out of my goddamn world,
take your punk ass somewhere else,
and be able to fucking live there, asshole.
but what you did is you came in here while I was having fun and you started mocking me again you
cock sucker and I told you right in the side chat I was going to let you live you little bitch
but now I'm not gonna because you constantly got to think that you're better than me JT
you ain't spit to me you can't carry my fucking job somebody said what he said he said I'm gonna
What's a little day's later the whole trolling cruise here if they're all here right now, dude, because I am every fucking one of them
Tenth wave of troll that has so I'm
Dural done. That's so bad in YouTube. I
Draw you right now as my first time meeting you I think you pot is I seen you were probably on one of you mess with a 1a community
You know a guy named Norfords you be on a guy named Norfords panel
NorCal?
NorFords
No, I don't
No, I do my own thing man. I'm not in a gang. I'm not in any
No, no, no, no, it's an old Thomas panel and I thought I saw you up there
No, no, no, I just do my thing, man. I just I'm just a standalone dude, man
Yeah, I just do my streams. I play guitar do some music fuck around
I battle people on occasion, but I'm not oh, yeah. All right. All right. Okay. Great. Great job
I need you up here to battle mr. But mr. Bigpipes
Uh
Here's the thing about big pipes that I know I knew versus big pipes all songs. They are legit for YouTube. Let's get it
And he plays the banjo, he's pretty good at it one second. So I'm gonna say I mean, I'll let you know
Rusty and Ziggy I think what I like talk to but um, so I'm bringing them up
But I just want like everyone just to be respectful. It's like not like
I don't want to talk to all of us. Talk to the panel. I don't want to talk. We really don't want to talk to these people, man. They're douchebags.
Yeah, let's just have a conversation. Let's keep the conversation going.
What do you think this is? This isn't an individual one-to-one call, sweetheart.
Ass suckers. Ziggy's an ass sucker for panel all the time. That's all.
This isn't a one-to-one call buttercup beret.
Now, Rusty's the brains of the
I
man. I'm talking to you. business. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get it all out. Let's get
This guy had a relationship with me for four years.
But not every relationship.
All the telephone is between our...
Oh, we got an angry X.
It sounds like an angry X so far.
Okay, let's go continue.
Of course.
He was completely emotionally dependent upon me.
I'm not emotionally dependent.
Everybody knows it.
everybody watched him and when I try to get rid of him, I'm the proudest motherfucker you've ever met in your life.
I'm not emotionally dependent on anything.
He might have been a small family if he didn't survive.
You are emotionally dependent on this man having devoted my fucking time in my life.
For four years
me personally
Personally, I don't I don't like my girlfriend unless she emotionally abuses me with another
The only girlfriends that I've ever had have emotionally abused me and I respect that
Hey, I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you. I was listening to you
You were supporting him and then he cheated on you and you're emotionally hurt
Hey y'all, y'all! Who's pushing better y'all? The new chick or the old chick?
I'm going to die. I'm going to die on stream. I'm going to die here too.
You guys, you guys are racist, you hate black people.
You guys are racists. Jarl is racist. Jarl is racist and he hates black people. Jarl is racist and he hates black people.
like to try and what?
Jarl's racist, bro.
That guy hates black people.
That's what you are.
Jarl's racist.
That guy hates black people.
That's what you are.
Jarl's racist.
That guy hates black people.
That's what you are.
I
Reading for these the same people
We're good. Yeah. Yeah. We can all
I bet that allegedly I bet allegedly is a weirdo that dog fights
how much you want to bet I bet money I bet money that allegedly is a word all
that pet that dog fights and I know niggas that have dog fights never like
That's why it changes its name because you guys can't go up to each other
And you're mad about that you jealous you weirdo
But okay, so jealous bro fucking weirdo
Like I felt like as soon as he left you had like a release right there you were like
No, you know, he was standing close a little bit. And it's like, I always have
This butter
I love it like I don't want to see it and I'll honestly I will smack that nigga like so hard, bro
Okay, yeah, I like I wouldn't I like
In respect in respect I would not smack him that hard not that hard
You're gonna sit in the city. What is that me? You would think me a baby?
Chill out, bro
300 chill out, bro
Bro 300 that's my nigga bro. I'm telling my needs. Oh, I'm chill out. Drop them. Sorry
My nigga, bro
Rochelle
Dude, I can't I can't I think a beer is that worth the shot take the I'll take a beer with you
Let's go
You know summer
Summer summer and Christine
Summer wait wait hold on hold on summer summer come up summer, but can we like hang out and like
I feel like every time summer hates me
Summer can we chill out some
I
look you can't even hold your head up sick
bro what is up with anything
hey sick you're on a panel look at yourself
you're on a panel with anything
what is up with anything
what is up with anything bro
wait wake the fuck up you're on a panel
alright bro
yeah I'm awake bro
come on
fuck bro
You never you never you never you never you never you never you never been
unconscious when I sleep I'm unconscious that's cause you know you're going to
sometimes you gotta be fucking he has to do
I'm no sick for a long time man and I'm gonna be there for a little bit. Oh, it's okay
Okay, sick. No, but you lean
Go to bed. I think he's having a problem. No
I'm still going. I'm still going
Your eyes are closed
No, it's over the night. It's over the night. Stop saying over
You're going to dreamland. You're gonna go to dreamland. You're hanging bro. So I'm so here. I'm talking to you
Okay, you're talking your sleep. I hate him, bro
You're
Wow
Maybe signals best if he gets some sleep or something
He's been moaning for like 20 minutes
When I'm unconscious, but you don't know
You don't know that you have more fun. You know, you have more fun when I'm on con
And whenever he put 300 in his title
So psyche has a going man
You know, it's like a normal day
Yeah, I got I got
can we do
that's what I was thinking
Yes, exactly
Well, I already don't like you
Damn bro, okay. Yeah. Yeah, it's like some money and shit. I'm never flesh money
Okay, well does it mean you're gonna donate to him or yeah, I
I just I kind of roll my eyes and people flash man
Drink the bottle I'm gonna buy you that's the only reason I'm gonna donate
Are you gonna buy me a bottle?
Yeah, I'll buy you a bottle if you drink it at one night
Um, I don't know about that. This is all a buck. Yeah. Yeah. Well, guess what say sure. Why did you put your wife on the phone?
At least the mission today forward my mission is to die from alcohol poison. No